Hi guys
Yeah, surely can Samantha
Is hear me, okay, hi how my ass chewed up again
Hello, yeah
just like woke up and fell right into it right into the audience good yeah I mean
there was just like a misunderstanding about you know did I pay Tracy best I
said I did of course I did she was in a different account she she realized that
If I say I did something, I did it, right? Yeah, I gotta go clear it up, but
the beat is just going off on me.
Hurry you saw in the video clip you saw someone on a video clip
It's like you know, you know you know in your heart already
Like you have intuition about it
So listen to your listen to your intuition about it
Also the high priestess is close she's cloaked, you know, she's very she's cloaked and so she might look different
They were different like without that the hat and the robes and things like that. So you can be missing mistaken identity or
Or you just or you actually need to recognize, okay?
But I'd say follow your intuition
You didn't know we're feeling
I'll be yapping it's my show. This is what I do. I yeah
That Jesus mom um
Hi, priestess. Well, she's uh, she's like I would say like a nun. She's like maybe like a high nun
You know, she goes with she goes along with the Pope
Who are they are the Hierophant Hierophant high priestess are kind of these intuitive?
intuitive men and women
So I don't know if Jesus mom, but she has a Torah scroll maybe maybe it could be Mary
She guards this garden.
Hey, what's up, Adam?
Oh, nothing.
No, it came out of the upright.
It came out of the upright.
Oh, yeah, nothing. You've been reading too much of the Talmud or something like that. I know those stories
I spoke to you. We know I'm out of weed might have a little few nugs left to my table, but
Just smoking tobacco
Hey rude
Cats are higher than I am
You're welcome
Yeah, if you'd like a more in-depth reading, you know
Happy to do free reading so there are the banner up if you're interested in a more in-depth anytime
I've done nothing. I've done that. I've done DMT. I've actually made it. I can make it myself and
Make it with the bark the mimosas still spark
Yeah on a on a
Slow cooker
I've made it
It's pretty pretty pretty strong stuff, right?
Hi rude rude sitting next to me. Hi guys
Did you see god or something you can't
Hear you can't get it here. Oh, okay
Well, are you in America if you're in another because in America you can
Then they can't get pure DMT usually it's but you can make it yourself
there's
There's videos on other websites the guy's making it. It's not very difficult
But it's kind of expensive a little bit expensive at least $50 for the bark plus you need all the other stuff
Yeah, so I
Don't know. It's like I sometimes I can't do anything right. It seems right
It's like someone's always being mad and
Even even good friends and stuff and so I try to like
Stay neutral in situations because I know there's a lot of stuff going on with other people and other
Relationships that I have nothing to do with that. I don't know that they've known each other for a lot longer
They have a lot and it's like
Pretty me and you're not even close to America
Yeah
If you can if you can see if you can order that bark it's called mimosa hostilus and they have some websites
You can see if they ship ship to you
And
You know check out see two videos. It's not difficult to make everything really illegal that the bark might not be legal, but
It's legal in America
Just tree bark is just bark from a tree
The DMT is in a few higher concentration and a few kinds of tree bark
And so especially the mimosas still has the most DMT in it
so
Was my phone doing
Maybe charge.
It's dead, oh no.
I died. I died so quick.
So just waking up. I had some crazy dreams last night
Crazy dreams
Oh
It's the end for this phone
Maybe I'll try to buy another phone tomorrow.
Let's put it down over there, complete charges.
Having problems.
How are you guys doing?
Let me see, yeah.
Yeah, I don't like, I don't want to hurt people. I don't want to like upset people.
That's what I have a fun show.
I look like a strung out ferret.
I think I'm very nice.
It's charging, it's charging guys.
It's a miracle.
We'll see the charges.
Let's strung out.
Even drink last night. Oh, yeah, I spoke to a little bit of weed that was left to my table and a cheeseburger a couple cups of coffee
I just woke up not strung out
You're not a terror reader believer it probably won't be worth I'd actually do free readings mostly
I do do paid readings. I've done over 2,000 about 2,000 of them on Etsy
I just got I got a message today cuz because someone I had mentioned my Etsy page and they went and they
They look at the reviews and some of the reviews referred to me as she like they say she
Because I didn't use my picture and I used just the business name
And I didn't correct people when they whatever they call me that it wasn't relevant when my sex is really but so say it's verified that
I taste everyone away. No, maybe I don't know. Maybe when everyone just hates me now. I'm not sure I
Didn't I don't think I did anything that bad. I'll try to just be fair be a friend to my friends
People get mad over certain things. I apologize
Lottery winning numbers, I mean some people might do that you can get a fortune cookie
You'll find numbers in there. I think those are paid off for some people before
Lady, I might just like it does it audio and video readings. You're a liar
No
You if you look at the meat if you look at the descriptions, they are written readings and
This is your admire
Myer of the cave
But it's the pave. I might have I might have altered it to you this year. I might have said I'll do video reading or something because
Of the goddess trees, you know her goddess trees, okay
We'll just check out this right right me there and right. Okay, right. You can right contact me and I'll write back from there, okay?
People have commented on her audio. No, they the goddess read. I've never done a goddess reading and audio the mire of the page
Then admire a page
You already contacted the seller. Okay. Well, you're lying Anita. You're lying. I can prove it
I can absolutely prove it
If you go to I don't know if I if you go to my psyche awakens returns. Oh, yeah
Well, nothing they can be sometimes general like it depends on like how specific a question you ask is and then it's like
I can get more detail, but a lot of people just want a general
Regaining and so it can be general. They're also
You have the message contacting the seller. Okay
Show me show me
Charge people the tea bag
Can I do butthole readings? Jokey jokes? Yes. $20.
How come you didn't receive the message that's my shot? I did. I got a message from Tripkicks.
Or not Tripkick or Tripkick. Do I have a buried screenshot is there? No.
I'll prove it. I can prove it on my phone. I actually, I don't know if my phone's charging.
But if you write me there, I got a message
for someone named Tripp.
They said, is this the person?
I said, someone named Psyche Awakens
is saying that they're you.
I wrote back and I said, yes, it's me.
I don't specify my sex.
You can enter the chat and made fight with her
about the terrible things being scary
than she did to you.
Well, that's, sometimes she read for you
and you didn't ask permission, that's a good thing.
Why do viewers refer to
Audio and video readings. No, they're actually just typed out readings and also I sent
Didn't ask if it's me and Tracy. I think it's going back Tracy. No, I'm fine
You just having a meltdown she's having a history of it crying she needs a break from it. Oh my gosh
It was because I left I mean I was there she I mean she put me back state and I was just like, you know
No reviewers specifically say audio right exactly
I didn't do it audio. It was an audio or video. It was written. It was written. I wrote them out and I sent sometimes
pictures
Hundreds referred to sellers because I just I didn't use my photo or anything
I just used the name metastike and sometimes people were
assumed terror readers are female
There's audio recording, okay, I'm very confused. I still know what that means like your specifically reference. No
I didn't do audio readings.
Show me a review that says, I love the audio recording I got.
I didn't do any audio recordings.
So you're wrong.
These are people.
It's very quick to check, guys.
You can just send me the message on Etsy,
and I can confirm.
But you're making allegations that are just ridiculous this they're putting this making people confusing people
Putting question people's heads, and there's no reason to anybody anybody can write me there. That's why do I advertise?
Why would I advertise a
Reader that's not me. It's just send them business
But I was doing those back in mostly 2000, 2001, or not
2000, 2001, 2020, 2021, when I really
didn't have a setup for doing video readings.
And it wasn't like the YouTube video readings weren't as a
big thing.
Like now I can just do it on YouTube.
I can do it over Discord.
At the time, I was just typing them out.
I did, I've done a few more since then, like, you know, I got into my account, back into
my account last year, you know, I just wrote my existing customers and stuff, I stopped
advertising on it.
The Wish Goddess is calling you to, especially our audio.
Reviews mention it.
I don't know, can you, can you just, can you copy and paste one of those reviews?
Just copy and paste one of the reviews and say, thank you for the audio reading.
Because I typed them all out. I can show you. I mean it's I can show you. I don't know if my phone's charging. Hold on
Yeah, it's charging
Yeah, but I'm not lying either and so I'm saying you're mistaken I can
You have to I was like go copy paste one of the reviews that says specifically that I used that I did audio
Can you just do that? Can you just prove it?
And I can explain because I have done a few I did a I booked a few readings from there that I did just do on discord through video
But I did it they know some of the comments. I know it's just it's just accusations and I need to dress up a psyche
specifically mischievous I mean, I just miss Cleo
All I can just I can just give a reading and I can say no
Get a reading from me get a reading from somebody else. It's a it's a metaphysical science
It's like can you prove even proof physics? You can't really improve regular physics much less
Now you say you do read videos. Yeah, I do and I but the whole thing was like I
Kind of don't pay attention to my Etsy store very much
I just keep it's up because it has my reviews on it. Oh
Come on that day
Well guys, you just have to talk to trip. I think it's trip kick
It might be somebody else, but I got a message for somebody named trip today on the Etsy store saying are you?
Psyche awakens someone's claiming to be you, but it says you're a woman and
References as a woman in the reviews. Okay, like I explained already
Show it
Me and my phone charge more and I will show show it
Oh, okay. Oh, okay. So I will copy the message that was sent to me. Hold on
So how would I get that message?
And I'm not on Barry's Discord.
OK, let me just charge my phone a little bit more.
I picked up my phone and now it's not charging anymore, shit.
Damn it, look what you bb do.
I don't have the app in my phone.
Okay, I'm not sending you the screenshot, I'm putting it on my Discord, my phone is
I'll add the screenshot from my store.
OK.
It's there on my Discord.
And here's my Discord.
about it, okay?
I post it on my Discord.
It is from my direct Etsy store.
Not getting it from somewhere else.
Wait, wait, I can't, so, no, oh, gosh.
You're just being a troll, okay?
to offer you proof and all you say is no, no, no.
Okay, thankfully, I found my other cord. Okay, thankfully
Okay, so there's my discord
Because I don't have the app on my cell phone and I'm using my tablet
Which has the app on it that had to take a picture off my tablet so I could do it I
Can download on my phone and get on my phone later, but right now my phone's charging
So
so guys are gonna stop harping on me
you can go write me yourself you write me yourself on the um in the etsy store and i will reply to
you and verify it to me so that can do
This is just people trying to say that but
Like I said, you can go read the 2000 reviews
I'm there. You can hear all the reviews in this
You know Tracy already told me
She made a mistake and I had sent her the money
I said a full refund for the kicking thing which has nothing to do with tarot anyway
So stop trying to put me in a corner. I know you're just all Kate's trolls trying to bother me. So
I have no, it's just ridiculous, it's ridiculous.
So if I just find one person that claiming I scam them,
can you find one person?
I would like to find the one person ever accuse me of that
Other than just trolls in the chat
I'll wait
Oh, my day is fine, my day is fine.
It's fine, it's just coming,
all these people coming at me with accusations
and it's like trying to like, just lie,
there's lying, there's lying.
Oh!
She was.
I didn't do anything to beat her.
All she said is I called her the B word
and I put her backstage once or twice.
That's what she meant.
If that little, that little something
will just destroy, can destroy a friendship,
it's like.
especially with your true friends you will make each other mad sometimes you know it's like but
you're not supposed to like just badmouth them and like say bad things about them and you know I
never said anything bad about her I just had a little argument with her I never I never bad
mouthed her I never said don't don't do this to beat it don't beat it shouldn't have this person
It's sad.
Hi.
Uh-oh, Mini Manson.
No
What do you mean? That's the way you mad at me.
Dying or dying?
Just fucking hide this too cold.
No, I'm not mad at you. I love you.
I really don't have energy to be mad at people like a like people are always mad at me
Like I'm always
You know, I'm a capricorn. I get scapegoated like I get blamed for things
I'm always cool. I'm wrong
No, not at all man since people will just try to search us try to stir up shit. Yep
People people that people just go back and forth all day between this person. Oh this person saying this about you this person
I just don't listen to people anymore about it. It's like I don't I don't really care to go and find out
Yeah
You're always welcome you're a you're a delight
Okay got that clean it out
Yeah. I mean, it's like, you know, life is too short. Hey, you're listening, but you're busy. Yeah, life is too short to hold grudges. It's like to be angry. And, you know, at least for me, it's like, I just want to cherish my time with my people.
Hopefully come on soon
Yeah, Arthur. Well, I don't know it need Anita was Anita was making accusations Arthur that were not true
So Arthur you could write me on the Etsy store and verify for everybody that it's me
And Edie came in saying, oh, well, everyone's saying that the channel, the Etsy store, okay,
the Etsy store that you mentioned, it has people that say in the reviews, they refer to you as she.
And I was like, well, when I...
they all call me she okay so i just remember being called she a few times but i was really
i was i just used a avatar it's most likely you who owns it you have access okay well now we're
now now we're just getting ridiculous so i'm in cahoots with that person hold on i'm in cahoots
with that person i mean come on now we're just getting ridiculous
sorry
What's up, so my bad you said you were saying something about Anita
Yeah
You can dive into that real quick. Sorry. I know you're down. Yeah, I try to drink
So so in 2000 I started at a store in Etsy and I started it and I was okay. I was very I was very
You know a little bit. I was shy at the time a little bit and I was like and until I just put I had a graphic
And then I was just I would sign my name
Meta psyche like the name of the store and I just and but I did goddess readings
I did spirit guide readings and most people would assume
Because especially on Etsy. It's mostly females anyway
I'm a female reader and a lot of people don't like male readers and so at the time
I was like, I'll just go with it whatever
And so yeah, and I was so sweet and I bet people are saying oh now they're saying oh well you're doing audio video
There's proof doesn't add up. We'll just Anita all you have to do is write to me on the Etsy store
You can just send a message request, but now everything I do I send a screenshot put on my discord
I said you can write me under there. They're like, oh, well you don't you so you just own the store somebody else
Like I have some employee or something that is doing
So it's like what doesn't add up is like why you're harping on Anita when I've already posted the proof.
I posted the direct the direct message from my disk from my Etsy Etsy marketplace messages.
And so they're they're my reviews.
There was a my readings.
Okay.
And I'm a gay guy.
And so I don't care if like I have a I have a female character.
Maybe there's drag there's drag queen terror readers.
And so just because you can you can identify yourself as a woman.
So, you can get away with it, it doesn't really matter.
Doesn't really explain the reviews, what buddy?
Now real quick though, this is the thing, psyche.
Sure, sure.
I don't think that's the real, I need a blunt in the chat.
I don't know, is that the real,
I don't think so either.
I've never seen that I need a blunt name like that
in the way it is.
And the profile photo is completely different
than what the usual one is.
Well, I don't know. I don't know Anita. I
Don't know. Can you send you some of your birth certificate? I need to see some proof now, okay?
I'll need to I need to get proof of your identity
You know, you're you could be some man you could be some man with the name I need some blood
I think you should give it a five to ten minutes if it's not if it's not providing any proof that that's a real Anita blunt
Yeah, go ahead and ban them real quick, you know, I'm gonna start
You know really enforcing some rules now going on. Yeah, let's enforce some rules, right?
We know we doing that over here fake any of the blunt you got five ten minutes
Matter of fact, it's 330 right now. I'm giving you another minute. It's 330
You to provide the proof or shut your face fake as any of the blunt
People need to start respecting the real guy here psyche
You guys are all here for the man for the show
Yeah
This would not be tolerated in Howard Stern
This is the third time there's like three it's already three things
I've been up for like less than an hour already like I've had the three accusations all these accusations made on me and
And then I say oh, you know you're you're bad person and it's like I'm not it's like they're just having accusations thrown at me
See what will stick and it's like
I'm uh, I'm getting tired of it, you know, it's like I'm with you. You know what your friend beta called me
What you know what she accused me of?
What she called me a pts. Oh, yeah, you told me about the story
Okay, yeah, I find that I that to me is not funny like
Fallen people your pdf just so you know, she thinks that's so weird to me
Arthur are you are you on my discord Arthur? I am not but I did see the link. I will be joining later
Okay, I got my tablet with me. I'll uh, okay
Somebody if somebody can go into my discord and just confirm that I have the message said to me this morning and my reply
On Etsy through my store and just to prove that it's my account, okay, and that it's me that is every reading
the
There you go
You don't give a fuck I said the reviews in there like I like I said, you know sometimes there's people that
Will think that I'm a female just because the way I talk, you know, all right
All right, where is it main chat? I guess where yeah the main in the main chat. It's the last one of the last
No, it's from discord look at my post or no, are you my discord yet? I put the link up. Yeah. I'm on your I see
All right, it says and really fuck nigga, all right nevermind that is the real I need a blunt
About you catch a brick with your face retard. He's saying I'm a fake accountant and whoa. All right, so
Psyche, I think we should get rid of Anita man. She's
Clearly it is the real one, but I'm not gonna say the f-word. She's calling you f-word
Okay, it's okay. I'm not offended not offended
But Arthur do you see like the post of my last post I posted a photograph if you can read that photograph on my left
On main text. Yeah, I mean text. Yep
Let's see. Okay. It's like I'm gonna read this it says
Hi. There is a man on YouTube who is claiming to be you. I just want to confirm whether or not that is you or isn't.
Your reviews refer to you as she, but this is a male who is claiming to be the owner of your shop.
He goes by Seiki Awakens Tarot on YouTube.
Yes, this is me, Psyche Awakens. I didn't specify my sex when doing these readings. So many people assumed I was female. I just went by meta Psyche.
Yep.
Hey, I mean, I don't know what, what is Anita trying to do here? Like, is she crashing out?
What is wrong with Anita, man?
And he just crashed it out as we speak
Be right back
It's the case of me having access to that ladies page, so I'm in cahoots with this woman, right?
That does she apparently does to the readings. I just I just have access to her shop
Damn everybody has Anita's back and I'm like, look at this, shaggy shh.
I know, but I just signed it and made a psyche.
I can show you a sample readings where I just signed it and made a psyche.
Yeah, Anita, it's a stretch, it's a stretch.
It's a stretch, Anita.
I love women.
They drive me crazy sometimes, but I love women.
Right? But it's all 45. They're all written readings. They're all written readings. All of them.
So I'm not going to say, oh, by the way, I'm actually a male. That's like, it's like, you know,
the person sends hymns for fucks.
I was joking. I was joking.
God. People are just ridiculous.
Looks like he's on the other line.
Okay guys, so if anybody wants to verify, you can send me a message on the reviewer comment.
She said, send him with her reading. How could you not know that it's on your page? A him with
her reading. Yeah, no, I send, I send like with the goddess readings, I would send the invocation
Or I would send a Bible verse sometimes maybe I like the Bible or a choker. I don't know
It's yes, I did every reading myself every reading
But it gets like you get you get weirder and weirder. It's like, oh, okay
Well, you said a screenshot. It's gonna change. No, well, that must not be your account
That must or you must be like have access to this woman's account. You really think there's this woman, but it's actually was just me I
Didn't know it because I was like the hymns. I was like did I send a hymn? I was like I sent invocations. I said like the Homerian
The Homeric hymns
Right, right clumsy
Yes, I said I said then some pictures of myself I said I said pictures of the spirit guide reading
It's I find a picture that I would match up with what I saw as their spirit guide, right?
And I was sweet because I must I'm a good writer and I write like a
person but you know you can't there's there's been women that have men that
have written books with the woman's pen name and women that have written books
with a men's pen name and they're saying oh it's that's not you because it's a
different name no it's called a pen name or it's called an alias or it's
called you know a business
Tell me the tell me tell me what the accusation is so you're so the accusation is it's not my store
When I'm and I already showed you I'm in this door
No, it wasn't it was a unisex name that people would just assume that I'm female because most terror readers are female
They go to the eighty ninety percent
They agree I'm a female. Well, maybe I'm maybe I have a female mind. Love a lot of people call me a
Lot of people say I'm very feminine feminine side
so
Not usually males that you wouldn't think a male would do a goddess or anything, but I'm very into the goddess, right?
Hey, Bronzeberg you got any bronze bird
Yeah, but I'm not catfishing
I mean, it's like because if my gender really has nothing to do with how I read or how I was communicating
But I never said I'm I've never said I'm a I'm a female. How about I didn't say hello? I'm a female
I never said that people just assume I
Encaptaged because I didn't use like a I knew some sexy woman's photo. I just used my logo
It's a butterfly on it, but I like or the the moth that has it the death moth
I don't have the logo still up though, but it was
You look like a woman, the bearded lady man, see?
But what you're telling me is there's no way I can prove it.
Because no matter what I do, I can fucking go in my back office
there and show you my registration.
I can do everything.
I can show you my emails where I just did all the readings.
And no matter what I say, you won't believe me.
So there's no winning.
So you just can't win, even if I'm right, which I am.
So, let's hold the same standard to everybody else, then, and it's like everybody else, whatever
accusations I hear about people, I do, I'll post a link, you can go book a reading and
I know, because the business really slowed down on Etsy.
I don't expect money from doing it.
I do readings.
Like I said, live reading, seven cards, $5, 13 Rees,
$10, and I also do free readings.
Okay, so keep your mouth shut then.
You don't even have to book,
you just have to write me there.
I'm gonna write you back.
Okay.
Then you say, oh, well, you're just yours. You have acts they're hacking this woman's page or I
Don't know
She all my all my information there and 100%
Okay, well
You don't have to but you don't talk in my chat public opinion
But you was harping on me at this point
So you don't have to be here.
Because on Etsy I would do these I would do written readings
because it was like not big yet to do video readings.
But now, when I, I'll say you can book through my Etsy store
and I'll do a Discord, a Discord reading, but.
Yeah.
She's just a hater.
You said you said I have access to this woman's page or something or I'm working with this woman. I don't know
And that's also you have to worry about guys is public opinion
Because there's a court of public opinion is a court of public opinion. Is that a legal court?
No, that's like a bunch of people spread talking spreading rumors, you know, it's not it's not legal
That's why I look I say well, where's the legal documents? Where's the legal papers your big whole woman
No offense is on about. What's up, Brandon? I mean, what's up, Psyche?
that
Are you doing?
Okay, how are you?
Can I ask you a question? Yeah
Why are you letting that towel head bully you?
Who?
I'm not use it. I'm not gonna don't don't don't call it be the names don't help me
I'm not gonna say it again, but you heard home. Don't call be the names
So why'd you say who if you know who I was referring to?
Because I thought you were talking to somebody in the chat like no, I'm I'm
I'm not gonna say it again fine fine. You heard no, I know I know I know you said
And you're be that as it may be that as it may I'm not taking it back
I'm standing by that
Okay, I'm again not seeing it again. No, I'm seeing I'm just I'm not I'm not taking it back
All right. Yeah
Like I said, why I'm I'll ask it again without saying the word. Why are you letting adjective bully you?
I'm not letting her bully me. I was you know, I was having a conversation or is this just a script
No, it's not a screw. I was like saying it's like her beard. Yeah, it's just a scrap. You're just a little bitch
Come on
Yeah
Goodbye
Anyway, yeah, he said he wouldn't want to say it's kick me while I'm down guys
I know
Hi, Root.
So Root's here.
Yeah.
I don't know, guys.
It's mad at me.
What can I say?
Hey, kiddin.
Yeah, it's a little bit piling on, you know?
It's like, oh.
It's like, it's like an injured animal. No, it has an injury.
Did you see Kitty?
It's a rude,
really old man cat.
Hi, babe.
It's a Rudy.
Okay
In second
Or should I put it on my pub on the main page, but I don't know if you want to in the private message. I'm sorry
You can do that, too
Hi, babe
Kidding
Fortunately my phone's working again. It's charging. Wonderful. Wonderful.
Hey, the charger must not be working too good.
Trolls will come.
It's okay.
Say something about what?
Sometimes like when people are just accusing accusing and then it's like you try to defend yourself and they're like
It's like even worse. How about nice like not how would y'all just ignore the allegations and a lot of people come up to their own conclusion
because I'm
Sitting there trying to defend myself over just blatant lies
Yeah, hello
Carmex
That's how to come cheer you up now that I'm in here to get on there
See if I click the link from the YouTube and I come on through that you'll have double audio and it will sound like 50 people are talking
Mm-hmm. That's why I put the link outside of the YouTube
We see here fine
Good to talk to you. Thanks for coming to cheer me up. It's just it's a little a little stressful lately, but I could see I
Don't bat ban anyone in your chat without your permission to because you know you gave me a wrench
But I just want to make sure like I don't know if you guys are close or playing until I really know what's going on
I don't want to ban you
Yeah
Yeah, and there are just like a lot there are a lot of trolls that come in my chat too and a lot of great wonderful people but
Yeah, if you feel weak or do you look weak in any way in their opinion that they will attack you? Yes
mm-hmm, and
I'm a I can be like a passive person, you know
California person in California people are very peaceful and passive, you know the older crowd like you know yourself and I'm 55 so
When I went there, I discovered it's a whole different world over there. It's awesome, too. I wish I would have grew up there
Yeah, it's a it's a nice place to have grown up and
You know, we've got nice weather and it's got you know, the people sometimes the people aren't so nice
Sometimes they are nice, you know, it gets very yeah, it gets very
Lonely you get low yeah, it's pretty low me here
That's like here also
Hmm, but I can see how California couldn't get lonely the weather's super there, but it gets bad there too. Just like here
Yeah, what do you have in head of dough doughnut don't know. Oh, okay. Oh an egg. Yeah
Looks good a good hard-boiled egg
Good morning. Well, it's afternoon now. I woke up this morning
Yeah, I woke up and then it's a bunch of
discount messages and
You know some things are cleared up some things aren't and some things are that there's more confusion people throw in there
And so, you know
Yep every day you'll wake up. There's gonna be something new you've got to deal with I
Don't know how long you've been doing the live shows. How long you've been doing this?
I've been doing the live shows for
for probably over six months and
I've been doing the open panels for like like five months for a basis in January
You're new it took me about three to four years before I finally found my niche in the internet
And where people were being cooled with me. So yeah, they're gonna trust you could
probably another few
Months to maybe two years. So just be ready
You mind if I bring another guest up or would you prefer just having us talk?
Well, who is it? His name is Arthur. He was he called in earlier. He was what not?
He wasn't the the shortlist guy. He was a guy, you know, yeah, okay. Yeah, that's fine
Okay
You know real quick my bad to Minnie real quick Minnie
Psyche I just wanted to ask
Did everything get settled with Anita Blunt?
Does Anita still trying to cook in like what are we doing with Anita now?
I I blocked her from the chat because nice nice like there's no need for that drama and the language my goodness
I've never seen Anita use that language
I don't know if you're in other people's this words, but I need to we just don't
Take a lot to get blocked in here
Anita do you kiss your mother with that mouse?
Got some kind of bad news or something possible
When people suddenly shift like that it means they got really bad news in their life. She's is like, let me let me see
Bad what she must have heard today
To recognize that because that happens to me
Yeah
I mean it's been really trying to dig up stuff, huh?
Yeah, but it's like she's it's like it's like there's no
What's what's that thing when there's no there's no smoking gun in the situation?
There's because I know the truth, you know, I that was my store. I very confirmed. Okay
the
But I just think because I was just an avatar basically I just had my avatar and I like you know
It's mostly women on that site. And so I'm not gonna correct them
You know sometimes they so I know this is my story was like I haven't I have a
It was under a business name. I just went by a business name. And so, you know, I've already confirmed written back
the person that I think tripped kick I think or something like that tried to confirm so I wrote
back and then it's like oh well you're in this woman's store you're like uh you're you're I'm
yeah it's like it's impossible to to to defend myself in it so it's like all I can do is just
show you the screenshot and that I own that store that is me that was me
Yeah, thanks, Arthur.
Yes!
How's everyone doing in chat?
We're here with Minnie Manson this afternoon.
So cool.
Yeah, I'm just scratching my legs.
That's why I turned up the camera.
But I'll turn it off in a minute.
Okay.
I used to be stretched on the ground.
A few little yoga stretches.
Mm-hmm.
To get my legs working.
Well, we had a we had jimmy rose on the other night and
I
Think she says hi. That's all I needed to do. Okay
Nice just a pre-order my dude. Yeah macaroni mom
Not gonna lose so
Yeah, you like some macaroni. Yeah, I get just really cool meals now
Better than meals on wheels and I get three times as much if not more
You know, I was getting meals and wheels for a year and it turned out the woman was stealing half
Exactly half of my meals. I was only getting six meals a week
This bitch with four kids
Around you know what's can't relax, you know, um, anyway, he was taking half of my meals
How fucked up is that we had to take food out of someone's mouth, you know
But she had kids and she was taking it from other people too. They found out she got fired
Yeah, I mean especially when you have kids like they you know, there are like a lot of other
Benefit programs when you have kids that they'll so there's plenty there you don't need to steal
You know, there's plenty there's a brand of mission and people used to
Want to help my dad do work just so they can steal and take extra things on the side
So I'm well familiar
Anything that has to do with helping a poor people are gonna go good jobs and that just so they could help themselves
They're gonna take your food
You got to be aggressive when you're poor you got to be aggressive about syrup surviving
Otherwise people will take your food
They will make you be submissive and look down at the ground
They'll shame you while they're stealing your blind and this is other poor people who do it
This isn't the rich doing it is poor people
Mm-hmm poor people with three ten times more than the rich ever will
Be true
Well, we have Stig as backstage. He was the second guy. He was he had the shirt off. I don't know
What do you what do you think about having him up to say hi? I don't know. Let's find out. Okay. Let's find out come on up
Many Manson knows who I am
This guy knows who I am. I'm a fan of his awesome. Thanks. How are you doing my friend? I'm doing great
wonderful
I'm just not a fan of psyches. That's why he takes offense to it, but it is what it is ladies and gentlemen
You're a fan, but then you love my you seem to love my show. It's like if I'm not a fan of the literally
Absolutely not ladies and gentlemen. I'm not a fan of your show. No offense
Well, I have you give you the respect to like give you advice. I'll give you the respect to like hey, you know
Why don't you why don't you want to take advice from someone that's not even a fan that's not even doesn't even like me
I'm giving you the advice out of courtesy. You don't have to take it. Oh, you're so courteous
Oh, my gosh, you're such a polite being courteous
Being said, I don't okay you as many man says cool though. I like that guy. He's alright
Well
I
Like he's just a little bit jealous
I lost up a very important thing. I was in a band. I
Have a lot of memory issues base because many Manson knows how to be a performer. That's something psyche never figured out
Oh, yeah, thank you
It's like he thinks the psyche thinks that I'm homophobic he thinks that I'm like against the gaze I'm not
No
Okay
Cheers
People use the F-A-G grt word. It's not that I do I do as well. I use a lot of words
Yeah, I know it doesn't mean I mean it's like people like I have people here like they say all day and night
I mean it's like and I I don't think if I don't think offense to it
It's like they say the n-word with the soft day. It's not like the many Manson school. All right. Come on, John
I you look I use the n-word with the hard R
It's just a word at the end of the day like that at the end of the day
It's just a word or a
Word it's just no freedom of speech in today's world. I don't hate anybody
If I hate you, you gave me a reason to hate you and it has nothing to do with the color of your skin or anything like that
That's to do with you didn't you?
macaroni
That's how it is good. It's good
It's how it is chat. Cheers, man. Buen Provecho. I also put up mini man the banner for
Mini Manson up. This is mini Manson's information if you'd like to say it gets here multiple times a day
But he hates it so much. I don't hate anybody here. I don't hate psyche
I just said that I'm not the like I'm not the biggest fan of this is all it is
Okay, it's not gonna preclude me from being here
Yeah, but it's like if I don't I don't if I don't like the like that
I don't like the the people on the panel like the host I'm not gonna I'm not gonna go to places where you know
I'm not you know, well, that's you psyche
Okay, that's me
I'm looking healthy. We're cutting we're cutting down on alcohol. Yeah, I didn't drink last night. We're cutting back on the alcohol
It gives me into too much trouble lately, but uh
Yeah
Know
Sometimes you got to stand on business. Yeah, I don't know what to say about that besides that we'll see on business. What do you mean?
She's gonna stand on business. You can't be like oh, I was drunk
I'm not
Growing ahead look wait
My nose is growing a nose on the side
Yeah, I don't know. I don't know if I'm drinking today either. I'm gonna come in as coffee crazy chat. Come on
I gotta make some videos tonight
You make some videos tonight. Yeah, people hired me to make some videos. I gotta get to work. Oh, cool
Hmm. I've seen some of your
Your music videos you put on your channel. They're very good. Thank you. My mole rap blues video everybody knows about mole rap blues
Am I correct?
At least you guys know about that one. That's my original song and I wrote
Entertainers will kill you and made videos of that and this woman came up
It's supposed to be my friend and she's telling me that she never seen it
I said well here it is then watch it now. She's like I I don't have time. I said you're not a fan
So she got black
Mmm, you said she got black black
Okay
Well, that's crazy
Yeah, it takes a lot for me to for me to
For me to hide anybody in my chat like sometimes my mom's do like unless but unless they're breaking like unless it's safe
Unless it's safe, then you'll cry like a little bitch and ban them right fucking stupid bitch shut up
I don't bad nobody unless it's safe. What the fuck up go ahead
Me right now bitch
You've gone. Oops. Thank you for being my family. Oh, that's awesome
Yeah, he's not a bad guy. He's not a bad. He's not a bad guy
And he's like, you know, just like, you know, and Alexander's not a bad guy
And it's like, you know, I still have SIG on again and again. He's poor and bomb me. He's he's
Said language that I told him to stop saying and he keeps saying it
He's calls me he calls me a stupid BITCH, but I still I still like him and I was like
i don't i don't i don't have anything against dig it's like he seems to that's not like me for some reason
and i do stand on business i i um i always keep my word people don't like people just for no reason
that's i've experienced that my brother used to tell me that it's sometimes i just be people that
don't like you just because you'll find us i'm trying to please them more than everybody else
you have to just give up on those kind of people and move on
Yeah, if it's meant for you to be friends later on they'll come back to you. Yeah
And it's but it's even friends even my friend even your friends will get more mad at you than your than your enemies and stuff like that
And you know, we mostly involved in our friends and so we'll get more seriously
And so it's hard when you have both your friends and your enemies are mad at you
It's like, you know, it's like I feel kind of feel kind of ganged up on sometimes. I know you know the feeling
When you have friends, you know, you will fight with them if they're good friends
They'll come back to you'll be friends later. It might take a while, but yeah
It's to take it's take more than just like getting a little little verbal squabble or like, you know
Because we all we'll get especially people spend a lot of time with we'll get emotional
We'll like, you know get mad for a second. We'll say words. We don't mean sometimes and then it's like
It's good to always come back and be able to apologize, and I beat up apologize, I accepted her apology, and I apologize to her, and then she's like, oh, apologize again for this, and it's like, well, it's like, I think if you apologize, all you need to do it is one time, and then accept the apology, and that's it.
That's fun to draw on the internet and stuff, but there's a such thing as doing it too much.
Yeah, I don't that's why I try not to go live too much and what I do
I have a purpose for going live like doing my artwork and then like that last night
I hung out with my fans for about a half hour after that
But if I just did it every day like I did last year just in like people didn't appreciate it. I could get boring
Hmm. Oh
Yeah, and I need I maybe need to
Lonely though. Yeah lonely. That's why you do it. Yeah
Because this is my social life basically. Yeah, this is this is like so that's why you know when I drank
I never had to drink alone. I'd always like you know, and I was like, you know be partying and like just like
See people I talked to you every day
Yeah, I wonder what would happen if all the people around the internet who are lonely if we all lived in the same town
If we'd all be hanging out I would all those people be on the internet looking for someone else to talk to
Mm-hmm. What if we took all ourselves and we were in a walled city and would we be friends with each other and all or would we just be
Looking elsewhere
It's weird. It's hard to find people in real life to hang out with. I've always been with you
Yeah, I used to have a friend for 12 years and then his brother took him away
He was a special needs person, but he was pretty intelligent. I
Mean he worked in stuff. I had a teacher. I was friends for like 14 years
Then I had lower Laura wasn't really my friend. That's a person. I knew I
hung out with that person for
Ten years and ten years of misery, and then I got in the internet now. I made a bunch of new friends
I don't need that person anymore
But it'll be nice to still have a friend here that comes over and hangs out with me, you know
Yeah, it's like having a pet, you know, but this is not the same
You don't have like someone you can go to the store with and talk to and help carry your jet and go to movies with
I want I need a friend like that
Or I could go to movies and festivals and shit and someone who has a lot of energy
Even though I don't have a lot of energy. I
Mean to have enough to go hang out at a festival for a few hours and all
I'm gonna go to festivals this summer. I'm gonna go of course to the Pride Fest for
It's two days in June
Mm-hmm. This one here. I'm gonna go to I hope I could go to this
Provided nothing bad happens to me this music festival here. Mm-hmm. Oh
Nice, who's you could click on this and take a picture of that if you want to go to that
Yeah, is that in Chicago? Yeah
Who's who are the headliner upfield right there by the red line?
But the Belmont stop on the red line, if you take the train, but the buses go there too and
there's a bar there, like a Jimmy Buffett Key West style bar called Trader Todd's,
where you could sing karaoke in there if you want. I did that last year.
Fun.
Yeah, they just had a this festival called the beach life festival here and it had along a s'more set and sublime and cake
I think and
Cake and sugar ray and so and those were like and I also like Bob
Not Bob Marley, Jr. But
I'm not fit to touch the hem of your garment
I like that song, it's from me, myself, and Irene, the movie, it didn't carry
And I'm nothing to touch the hamburger garment
That's the part when Charlie Bailey gets just snapped and he just crapped on some guy's lawn and started just going nuts on everyone
I
Think I think I saw that years and years ago. I need to need to see it again
And then in the movie with Charlie Bailey gates, but then he developed like a second split personality
Yeah
Well, that's, I need to see that movie again.
Yeah, I like the chats calm down a little bit.
Yeah.
Over, they just been on my ass.
Like, you know, the chats is the,
a lot of people, oh, you did this, you did this,
do this, do this, do this.
And it's like, I'm just trying to run my show and,
you know, if people-
Well, don't do that.
Tell my story.
If they don't get narrated,
it'll get worse this moment.
Yeah, I'm gonna try these that's out. Wait. Let me see. What are those tomato lime or toasted?
Twisted lime. I can't wait to try that.
Sounds good.
Got it.
I love lime on tortilla chips. I love those Doritos. I love the Doritos Locos Tacos at Taco Bell.
Tacos Locos.
Do you ever have the Doritos show?
You're so good.
Doritos or triangles got to be careful when you eat those stuff. Fuck your mouth off
Yeah, I want you to have my gums when I was in high school
I ate a Dorito and it made a big huge cash in my gums
Yeah, they are sharp. They're sure about that. I sew it now. I'm a millionaire. That's why I have it now. I'm kidding
Let's see what's down. I don't think I have a water. Let me go get some water. I'm gonna sit in the front porch and talk to you
Okay, great
Because it's nice outside when I get some soft
Until like that
Yeah
This is where I film my videos guys. Look there's my stage
Hmm, you know you want it
You want to see some of the coloring book before I go outside? Yeah, let's see it. Okay, let me put this stuff down
And then our judge would be carrying this and something
And you can't turn the camera around on this so I have to
Put the stuff on top of it
Love to move a little step on the way because I'm gonna be filming videos tonight
And I'm gonna need that area. Mm-hmm. So let me move that
Yeah, feel free to watch my lives when I
Listen to my artwork
We're gonna throw this in me too. I didn't see that. Oh, yeah
Okay, I have another cigar
I want to get some of those clothes cigarettes. Well, they're black cigarettes. Mm-hmm. They have a little red triangle on them
Okay, well, here's a pencil version of my work here. There you go. I'll put it on full screen. Oh, yeah, do that. That's a pencil one
Wow
You know you want it
I'll put the camera sideways so you can see it more when I do the sideways ones anyway. Let's see
Yeah
What's that was that that's a guy, this is a bug. This is what you call um
What is that called a thousand leger that's great being my fans named in that let me see here
Look how thick this is that they're gonna be on card stock
It's getting the book is gonna be a stick as this when you get it. It's $30
I'm gonna have this done by the end of June
My dentist is better than yours
Oh, here's a sideways one, so turn the camera sideways so you can see that
There you go. There you go
So those words on it, you know, you know, you want it this one has double block of words
Mm-hmm. It's Mike is going right down my pants. I just took a lump in the draw
It's got all these little details
Shit like that. So, you know, you're getting your money's worth. You get it. Definitely. It's two free stickers will be put in there
Let's see how many I've done so far one
two here, let me put this up a little more.
That, three, four, five, six.
Got that one.
Oh, cool.
Seven, eight, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine, nine.
as he'll see yeah i love it nine
very cool and i've done 10 pages so far and there's like 52 of them oh here again it's in
That's perfect. It's a perfect like the details is perfect for coloring book
I think that's gonna make this a perfect coloring book. I'll look at the cat there. Yeah, that's why everything you look at us like
Where's all the dark?
There's a black areas you are gonna add
Everything including your own shadows
That'll be a fun coloring book
Smack y'all we're here with mini Manson this morning
Hang it out. So let's put that in here
Turn that over to protect it
Yeah
So my streams are very peaceful
When I'm doing my art or sometimes I'll be drawing and I won't be saying anything
But I try to say something, you know, so that
YouTube doesn't strike the video for being inactive I
Told my friend Dylan that he believed me
I said you can't be it cuz like he'll go on there and
He'll turn his video game on he's like 33 years old. He's in a group home, you know, so it's a little slow
If you know what I mean, so he'll turn the video on
As game and then he'll just go to sleep or he'll go do something else with the game just sitting there and causing
And so I told him that it was against the terms
Service of YouTube to have your video just being stagnant and no voice on there. I said they could strike this channel
Yeah, who's gonna sit there and watch some of these videos, I mean why go live if you're not even gonna talk
Well, there are people that do sleep streams and they you know some people like to watch people sleep and stuff
Yeah, I make some of the I have some of those. Yeah
But I agree
I was joking with him. I was kidding around and he believed me
Jamie Rose's a chat saying hi everybody. Oh, hi Jamie
I'm gonna pop up here. Jamie. I think the link is pinned if not, I can post it again
Say hi
How's everyone doing? Yeah, and so yeah, yeah, so hi mini
I was just putting some stuff away here.
Like I said, tonight I have to work in here.
I need two hands for this.
Yeah.
So I do know a lot, I do know a lot, a lot of people that have this done, they've done, they're basically called bass streamers where they'll sit there like watching TV, like, you know, Benny kind of would do that a lot, he would like sometimes just go and get kind of stoned and like stare at the TV.
And his video games have pleasant sounds in them too, so it's not the end of the world, but I was just messing with him because it was fun.
Like I said, it's beautiful beautiful music that you could fall asleep to
Mm-hmm, yes, so
Yeah, you should listen to the first two are identical, but I have a different picture in them
And yeah, because I can't I don't know how to make them an hour long so
I just made a second one. So when I fall asleep, it'll just automatically play that one too
Yeah, one more. We got one or two more views and I have six six six views on that one video
Go ahead. No, you know, I used to fall asleep. I listened to Howard Stern
Eric the midget called I don't know if you ever listened to Eric Eric the midget. I know some of those clowns from
Howard Stern, I really don't get along with them too well. I don't like the whack Packers
Yeah, he was a whack Packer, but he passed away, but
He was he was like three foot five and he was obsessed with American Idol and like Kelly Clarkson
He was obsessed with WWE wrestling and then they started sending him to the bunny ranch
I don't know if you know about the bunny ranch, but I have no idea what any of that is
The bunny ranch is it's a brothel in Nevada. It's like a legal legal brothel and so yeah
And so he would send him to this bunny ranch a kid. I'm late
And they're like they said they said when the girls were marching down to his room
They look like they look like they were heading to a camp
Except for the shape except all he needed was shaved heads. That's what that's a joke
but
They um, but yeah, but then he uh, he had like a little
He had a six-foot-tog handler named Yon.
And then he wouldn't let the like yawn sleep with the women. He was he would get jealous. He didn't want to share
Oh, he was obsessed with Diana de Garmo and
Let's see who are these wrestlers. There's a bunch of a bunch of ww wrestlers
He got him on TV shows. He got him on like one show called in plain sight with Mary McCormick and he had these like little roles
He'd be in his wheelchair. He was in a wheelchair
He was just like, you know his hands were his hands were kind of like, you know webbed a little bit and
you know, he just had like the worst hand dealt in.
Oh yeah, so someone remembers the disaster stream with Alisa. That's the first that's
where I first saw you. I saw you, she was interviewing you and she kept calling you
mini by the wrong name. Disaster streams, I would call it that. You know, anybody who
hangs around Alisa is going to meet with disaster. She's done that to too many people.
If it was just me and two other people.
in all the years of her stream and I was I would tend to blame my stuff
It's just seeing how she treats other people and blaming myself for all
Well, I do know I know she has a lot of falling out to people, you know, I am
Yeah, she's you know her channel hasn't had any new subs or growth in the last six months. It's stagnant at 19.4,000
19,000 point four, you know, so
She's just boring old lady talk it even her her moderators and a lot of her fans are just
Boring old ladies and when I started
Accumulating those kind of fans. I saw fuck this. I have to do something and I started changing up some shit
And now everything's getting good for many again. I get in a badass rock and roll rebellious fans at a rock star craves
Yeah, the rock after all ladies want to come after that. That's great because then they know where I stand
Well, I think it's important like you know because it's like I was concerned about numbers
I'm like liking the numbers
But if like a hundred people are in chat and like everyone is like hates me
It's like I'd rather have like ten people that that like me and we revive and it's like such a better energy
And so it's not all about this a quality over quantity with like the people that follow you because there's a lot of people that are just trolls out
There's looking for like the next
I have ride hat red studios. Give me a heart. Yep
My eyes are really bad, especially when I look at the thing on the phone, but I could see that
Yep, and yeah, Hacker is a great friend of the show and they are also
They're doing them the they're playing all the Eric Eric the actor called see that
But these he called in over over a period of 10 years
So there are like literally hundreds of hours of like this call one time he negotiated like he
It's a cerritos. Yeah
He negotiated um he had a contract because they put him on the show
He's like he demanded like a full limo, which is like more than the actors got
He said a five-star hotel with a pool and a masseuse and then he demanded these coca-cola's he said like
They had to negotiate down and like and like they're like okay
Well, we'll send you a car. We'll put you in like a nice hotel in the area
And they're like they don't give you your we'll give you your two two two-liter coax and then after the show
He wrote them and he said he said he was kind of ran with run with this mafia guy
This kind of mob a related guy named Johnny Frodo
He's like he's like I'm gonna have Johnny come talk to you because I didn't get my two two liter bottles of soda a day
And so I he's like I
Body I would have demanded all that shit, too. I want my limousine
Hotel with the pool and all that in a misuse
Yeah, I saw these two limos yesterday when I went up to the store up there, but I'm more
Not more
Irving park they were parked on Irving park across from the store
And these are the longest stretch limos ever seen in my life. I mean they were fucking like
I swear they were like 30 40 feet long
I never seen limos so long
They weren't limo bands either though. They were a car like
Lincoln's and there was two of them. I took pictures. I'm gonna post those
On my community tab once I added them
I took pictures of me with it behind me, you know, and all they were huge
that's like
Metallica kind of rock star limos that I saw they were white. I
Love limousines. I'm gonna use them as a dildo
Yeah
Well limos are
Not if you want to get some acts and what many you got to send a limousine
Say and it has a pink champagne in it from Corbel
mmm
Love a good pink champagne
Well, we make up my sister makes on Christmas. She makes or like she makes these either
Parma granite pomegranate and and prosecco you like for seco
Yeah, yeah, how much a pomegranate little bit of pomegranate juice, but I did
Docs
Are you doing yeah, he's back. He's back
He's my favorite homosexual, which there aren't many how much sex please take that as a compliment
Okay, I think it is a compliment. I'm your favorite one, but you don't like me very much though. So
That's crazy
Casey
Oh, yeah, I should you I should with Casey Armstrong. I'd love to I'd like I'd love to shoot case Casey's from Howard Stern
Yeah, but you gotta stop being such a softy
Because you have to understand sake you got to think about it, right?
Put yourself in the position of psyche. Okay
You think that these Howard Stern people aren't gonna try to punk you out? Yeah, well
You think there's oh
This guy's so cool. Yeah, they're gonna punk you out. You think you're pumpkin me out psyche
Psyche you think you're pumpkin me out putting me backstage. Listen little bitch. They're gonna punk you out much worse
We're right. Okay sick. Thank you. Oh, thank you. Okay. Go ahead. I'll see you later. Okay, so anyway
There but I'll say is like I've met a lot of people for Howard Stern and
Like, you know shooley the producer. He rated my show and it was a big friendly raid. He was kind
You know, I get along well with the you know, JD's a producer of the show
There's other people I've met through of your Howard Stern
I'm a big fan.
They never punked me out.
Yeah.
Elisa's chat has kind of turned against me.
Elisa, I used to get along well with Elisa's chat,
and now they're like, you know, she allowed me to post
my channel and her Discord, and I posted a couple of lives,
and then they're like, oh, you have, you have a city,
shitty show with like a, and you stream at the same time
as her, she knows.
She's let me, she's let me stir my screen and call into her
Several of them several times and so I've never been mistreated. Let's treat or anything or punk down
I've been punked out by other people's communities and stuff, but
You feel like a punk
Like a punk, you know, I'm like, but you know
Incense I used to recall those punks when we were kids. We'd like fireworks
But what what what what are what is that what is a punk like what is that?
You like firework, but we call them punks for some reason
I mean
You let the fireworks with it, you know, just like an incense. Oh, yeah. Okay. I guess I guess yeah
Take a
That was like in the 70s 80s
You know the good old days before I left Palo Parque
Well, we went to Puerto Vallarta a few times and my brother would go to like he would like to tell the cat cab driver
You know take him to the fireworks store and that he would drive about an hour away
You come back with like a can like a cannon basically there are these professional like fireworks like there and they were just crazy
My brother was a fireman
fireman technique
So I know about fireworks a little bit
Yeah, but I love fireworks. They're really cool. We have a big big fireworks show off the pier
I'm not cuz I'm right off the ocean and so
Fourth of July there's just like the full their disguise full of these really
It is so cool
Mortars and whistling bottle rockers and anything colors that spins
Nick go up a nickel
Yep
Even love even the sparklers. I love I love like a nice sparkler that burn my leg with sparkles. I still got the scar
Yeah, I remember I touched I like you know
You know it out and I touch I touch the area and then it burned me real bad
You know, there's a lot of people like I've had accidents with fireworks to be very careful
And so I would always say use one of those punks to use a punk to light it because I know a lot of people
There's some malfunctions and stuff
Okay, sick sick what you call me a bitch you're coming to the link, right?
share
Madson keep this guy many Madson keeps sending me his dick pics dude. Come on. That's not me
It's like with you in your face in the same set
that's not me
Blocked that account where we're still in it and many many Madsen was saying that he was enjoying my thick brown Mexican cock
No, he I think it was just a bad attempt to see that that's not funny. It's not funny. Yeah
Don't do that to me and you could do it to anyone else, but not me
Say yeah, do it to him
Yeah
Yes, let's say do it to me. I'm not feeling
He's trying to be provoked and he's trying to know it's just kidding around. Yeah. Yeah, he's kidding around
But you can tell my hands are busy. I'm outside my computer is up there
I can't put nothing in my phone while I'm on the show here because if I went out of the
video I would end up going off the panel yeah yeah we know we so we've seen
your hands you're eating chips and reading reading stuff and we've seen you
all the time yeah he's just being outrageous yeah many can do no wrong
right that's true yeah who's your favorite entertainer yeah many manson
and
very talented talented musician and
It's and performer singer and this entertainer in general
Can you see that? Yeah, I like what can you real woke up the coffee tops?
Uh-huh
Whoever someone sold the coffee pots. Someone stole my coffee cup. I'm headed to the police station and look at mug shots
They said to follow your dreams. So I went back to bed. Well the American dream you have to be asleep to believe it guys
George Carlin is my favorite comedian
I do a mini-maxin. Oh, hello, I'm okay
That's J-Dog J-Dog is a friend of the show so awesome
To the thief who stole my glasses, I will find you. I have contacts
Okay, well, this is funny
Love it good
Very cute
What's read another one? Is there another one? Yeah, there's other ones. I put my grandma on speed dial. I call that Instagram
I call Instagram pentagram
When does a joke become a dad joke when it becomes a parent?
Very good you got any you got a good joke J dog
I
Have a joke so so a vampire walks into a bar
And he goes to the bartender and he says can I just have a couple hot water and the bartender is like
Watered why hot water don't you drink blood and then the the vampire takes out a tampon puts it in the cup and says I'm making tea
I
Okay, yeah, I'm sorry
That's enough to kill you all. Okay
That's the only joke. I know by heart basically. I know
Like that, but did you get a chance to see beat a stream earlier this morning? Did I yes, I did I was I was on it
I was on it
Okay, so you guys are okay? Everything's okay? Yeah
She's very mad at me still but yeah, I just wanted to make sure if you guys are okay. Yeah, all right
We're all I'm all good. I'm all good. Okay. I don't I don't I don't I don't hold madness to her
Hello
Charlie horse, oh, I hate when I get those that's the worst place
It's Charlie horse, that's funny that when you get older and you get those it's worse
Yeah, that's when they come
Yeah, there's been a lot of drama today how baby my neighbor's family
that's nice you said they give some friendly neighbors
Yeah, don't I forget to mention I have kids and I'm okay
Later we didn't know
Oh ice cream I
Hope that comes by today. Okay dog drives an ice cream truck. Yeah
Ice cream in
They don't know I'm live. It's funny. Okay. That's funny.
So
There's been a lot of drama today like already like you know, but it's like a lot of it got cleared up
But you know, I like yesterday I said, oh, you can check out my Etsy store. I've done like 2,000 readings on it
You can see the reviews and some of the reviews say refer to me as she because a lot of people just assumed
I was a female doing the readings and so I've already gotten emails say is you are using the same person
I've written back from my account and then
people don't say oh my god like I'm doing something so wrong you verify it yeah
but the reason I was asking is because
you remember on the screen like a couple days ago when you showed me like a screenshot or kind
of like a receipt or something like that on your phone saying look at like people are asking in the
chat like did I pay back somebody and look look it's there like can you show something like real
quick like look I paid something
I don't remember what it was exactly or anything like that. I just remember it was some kind of receipt paid to somebody
Yeah, that was about the tracy and tracy
Still like telling you don't answer your phone or someone calls what the fuck
Well, my phone number's been put out there
And so I get a lot of a lot of calls a lot of text messages some are some are not so nice some are nice
And so it'll say it's a scam on there
And it'll turn out to be something that you need like your doctor or something
So now I have to answer all the calls and if I hear a beep sound like whoop and nobody talks for three seconds
I know to hang up on those assholes
Yeah
It sucks to be you for the hesitating when you call me on the phone
Did you report me to the FBI? Some of people are saying that in chat
You know what happened I was just on groupie Jimmy's channel and I was explaining what had happened
Oh, cool. Groovy Jimmy love. Oh
Oh, yeah, I know
Yeah, you have to lift you lift you lift your shirt J dog and prove you're not wearing your wire
You have to lift lift up past your nipples
No, I don't want to look at nothing. Okay. Okay. Well, that's good enough. That's good enough.
Fucking fuckers. Also, nothing. No wire, nothing.
I was just trying to get you to pull up your shirt, but it's okay.
Hold on your pants too, it makes you just wear it there.
Yeah.
But.
No, I haven't had a problem this is January.
of this year. I had people who were law enforcement and they had
questioned me about stuff online like asking me do you know who Gruby Jimmy is
who is he to you and it was somebody who had reported me and him and a few
others
to the FBI saying that we were making
terroristic threats to get people, which was a lie.
It was just a lie.
But the FBI show up and actually interview you.
Yeah, they they questioned me they did. Oh, cool. What are they professional and really awesome?
Yeah, no, they were they were cool like they were good guys like I already knew who they are very smart intelligent and
Professional you always talk to them. Yeah, they were and you know, I had nothing but respect for them
You know, I just thank you. That's right
Yeah, and you know, like I said, I had no problem and then they were just asking me question
Like, you know who this person is, you know, and I go, yeah, they're they're internet friends of my I go wife
They go well
You know they said that you are making characteristic threats on a panel. I go who's panel they go we can't tell you I go well
Unless I have proof then you know up unless I'm under arrest or unless you know
You have a restraining order or you have a you have my name
Did my name come up at all in the talk that my name come up ever? No, no, this is before I even knew you
This is after having up making a presence on the internet. That's good. No, this is before I even knew you psyche
Okay. Yeah. Okay. I'll take it. I'll take your word for it. It's okay. I'm not doing anything wrong guys and stuff
Yeah, that's the truth. So now they're trying to they're trying to twist the story up
From what I said on Jimmy Jimmy's channel
Is that Kanye with a porn empire? Let's say Kanye is porn empire
Yeah, Kanye, they're porn empire. I'd like to see those people walk about it's funny
Yeah
Connie lost it when he was in like that. He was like that that a Balenciaga mask
He was on that show just in a mass
Growing up in Chicago is hard and that's probably why it's PTSD
Actually, he had to live in a project's Cabrini green in the Robert Taylor homes and I'm from Chicago
So I've seen that first hand that shit was horrible. I'm glad that's all that shit down
But you don't forget a thing like that
It's probably what
That's why I went crazy later on
You know, he doesn't have to worry about living in that shit ever again no matter what
Even if he never has a sponsor again, he's always gonna get royalties for his music. So I was gonna have money
It was smart enough to make an empire for himself. I wish I could do that
Well, you can and you're
Well, it's like there's always like, you know, there's always like building the empire and there's always you know
That's like just like this this my show is like, you know, it's a small like little 2,000 subscribers, but
I'm slowly, you know, keep going and keep streaming meaning new people going on other panels
putting my name out there and it's like and you know
I'm kind of well known in some communities, but it's like I'm not I'm just a small little fish
And so it's like the people get the open arms about my little channel like my little
I have a friendly channel where I do tarot cats and like have interesting people and so
The internet makes everybody a star overnight, you know, famous people watch my shit. They don't comment a lot of people that are
mega-famous
And at least they can't really the only thing they could do it's like that you wouldn't give me a contract to shit like that
Let's say their own record label, but
They could help me by
you know
Going public with me. Let me meet with them and once or something and oh, hi
and
I'm surprised that you haven't been asked to do like a reality a reality show
I think you'd be such a perfect character on a reality TV show and like that would really put your name on them
Even the more in the map. Oh, look at your flutter. There's something there
You know, I'm just flying around in the air. It's fucking beautiful. Let me put this mail away. I can still hear you now
Okay
Yeah
Yeah, but I want to I want to like
I want to continue going with this show and just like, you know, it's like a lot of fun and I can I encourage everybody that wants to like, you know
wants to
Make friends and and get out there a little bit if you're not shy and stuff
They can do your live streams and give people a platform. You know, it's not easy. It's not easy
You know, but uh, you can actually meet a lot of people a lot of really cool people. The good outweighs the bad definitely hi, Ivana
Dude, just like our new bro. I didn't appreciate him the other day coming on. That's cute
You're trying to do, you know, you're starting out, you know, everybody knows you're starting out, but it's like trying to
That's like trying to be mad at the baby for crawling and say, why aren't you walking yet?
Well, you got to start slowly, you know, you got to do baby steps, you know, it takes one step at a time, it don't happen overnight
Sometimes it takes years, sometimes it takes decades, you know, it just depends
And that's even constructive to say anything should be good. It's so beautiful very
very sweet
Oh, yeah
John Wick
That's how nice she looks there with his clothes
Keanu
Good-looking guy, and how old Keanu uses
nice clothes are
Keanu Reeves is 61 years old or 62. He's around 61 or 62
Celebrities can do no wrong. I want to be more of a celebrity so I can be perfect. Yeah
Yeah, they kind of get the
You know, I remember that you said the inquire. I mean, they sell the inquire the star and they would you know
But they were basically kissing the celebrities butts a lot of times sometimes they'd have like, you know
Pictures without you know people like Julia Roberts pan man or say with other makeup and stuff like that
But yeah, I look good without makeup. I've seen like me. Yeah, I don't think I look good without makeup
When I put that shit on and it's really good
Hell I gotta put this here for a minute
Yeah, we got the sirens
I fucking hate sirens, man
All I last night that's all I heard
There must have been a bad accident down the street. I mean it was like for an hour
You remember the shooting mini-man so when you're doing that live
Yeah, I know for signs and all the other members
That was crazy that was wild I was got killed
that was so crazy
The guy came back around the suss about the threat or not. Yeah
I
Just put my head down like that and I put my phone up and I just kept walking
I need a key drove off because he's turned his car and came back through the parking lot of the gas station and
Looked at me and I was just like this, you know and thank God. He just went his own way
Yeah, he wanted to make sure nobody saw anything or nobody. Yeah, you were just minding your business kept walking. That was it
Yeah, he had no idea I was filming for all he knew I was on the phone with my friend, you know, yeah
Most people don't walk around filming at one in the morning. I was the only person over there, too
Yeah, it was it was really a
Wild that night. Yeah, you were putting up signs for your yard sale, right? But yeah, yeah
But yeah, that was crazy many man shows putting up signs in it. I know we just hear we just hear pop pop pop like
And everybody was scared like asking of many was okay
And you know that stuff goes on all the time that scares me less than some other things that go on around here
Oh, wow
Like someone walking down the street is more liable to mess with you than someone from a car
Yeah
Yeah, well, that's that's scary. That's and I know Chicago Chicago has a lot of a lot of violence going on in Chicago
The trolls never come here. They're too scared
Hey, everybody
Yeah, I had a roommate from Chicago my college roommate was from Chicago. Oh, really good college
Yep
And then
People are walking by now. There's a school over there. It's like a performing arts school
I'm telling us I didn't get to go to a school like that grown up
They used to punish you for being weird in school
Creative but that that was spin because I had to go to this Christian school for a while
First public school and the Christian school and public school then the Christian school my dad kept waffling on that
I'm glad I got to go to both though because it's different
Yeah, I got to do I got to do like a community theater like we think they had like, you know for like
Like younger like you know between probably 10 and 14 years old everybody was in these plays
We did like sugar, which is like some like it hot. I don't know if you've ever heard of that
That's Marilyn Monroe movie. Yeah, I was in once upon a mattress, which is like this
Very princess in the P. It's like a funnier version of princess in the P and then I was in bye-bye birdie
I played Mr. McAfee and Bye Bye Birdie. So this is the three big plays I did.
I can't wait till I'm in this magazine.
That means it's somebody irrelevant when you're in an inquirer.
It won't always be like flattering though.
That would be cool. So are you are you're a show cut for someone someone named silky? It says is that mini from silky show?
Yeah, there's only one mini man. Yeah, I'm the one that strikes his video
We have this thing where I get naked and I strike his channel. He likes that too
He actually does like that you can ask him. He thinks I'm so hot. He says it on his show too
But I can't get naked too much because his channel would go bye-bye if it was too much. Yeah
Well, I saw you I saw you
Let me know I
Saw you moon Elisa once I saw I saw you you called
Was if I go on a show I'm gonna be naked
I
Well, I think I was I was I was there I was there for a little of that and so I saw I
Didn't see the link. Yeah. Yeah, I
Saw it. I was like, yeah, and so I mean I call in and I'm you know
I I said the song once in a while too. She you know, she's really into the the Muppets and you know
She's in the Muppets and like and so we're both
We're the 80s 80s babies and so and I've seen that song
the one Paul Williams wrote rainbow connection and she didn't even like that
I think she did she didn't have the guts to admit it
okay because you see saying that on my you sing that on my show too and I loved it
why are there so many songs about rainbows rainbows got nothing to hide
I'll you'll be surprised that rainbows can hide that murder over there, you know and
That tax fraud over there. Just put that color will rainbow up there. They won't see the corpse
Colors just right they won't even see the body
The kind of dark but it's true dark, but true that energy shit is real
There's also a show called picket fences and oh the and somebody I forgot who there's like one of the
Deniales of the you're here picket fences and someone's saying that song on that. Oh, I love that show. Oh my god. I wish you put that in to be
Yeah, I think it might have been I love picket fences. Yeah, old Jewish actor on there that I liked and and also
I'm scarred. Who's one of my favorite actors all time. Mm-hmm having drac
it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it
That's one of my very favorite bands of all time.
Stephen Nick's Love.
I love that song, Little Lies.
Some of these women are awesome.
Yeah.
You can't start a fire.
You can't start a fire without a spark.
Whoops, I'm thinking of something else.
Our cool principle.
Our family says.
Art says that he is your mini's mole rat song. This is his favorite
Thank you. Anybody who knows about my mole rat song is a true fan and mini loves you
If you don't know about my mint my song by now, there's something fucking wrong with that
You know, I love when people cover it and when they sing it when they use it to troll other people
That's just like the beat and everything. I just that song is just so perfect for me
I can even play it on my guitar
I'll play it for you on my guitar when I get that shit fixed. I got to take that to the music store
That's good wrong at the calibration of it. I can't even tune it no more
It's mini now that's entertainment very many yeah, yeah, that's right
So I gotta say Bill Billy is a mole rat. It is a certified hit. It's a banger
Billy mole rat
What inspired you to come up with that, but it's absolutely genius
It just came out of nowhere bill was being like a racist and shit and I just like
Because people are calling
It's so catchy
Thank you
So I saw Jay, I saw Jay dog up here. Uh, you gotta stay away from that guy
Many he's not good. He's the type of guy. I'll try to take your career and you're too talented for that
We can do that long way over here on his way over there. So there's no
See that's that's the right attitude
Yeah, J-Doc's literally been sitting in that one corner for eight hours today.
Like if it's his job, it's really pathetic, Benny. You're way above him. Absolutely correct.
We're above most people. I'm really humble.
I see that. Look at Suck sitting over with a giant smile on his face.
Like he's in the presence of a celebrity.
Yeah, I can imagine why everyone's crossing the street
Yeah, but you have fun out there in the porch, right? I'm probably the least threatening person in this neighborhood
How often you when you're out on the porch you just yell the n-word just for no reason at all and we're never
I was kidding around
I can't put up my rebel I said I need help putting up my rebel flag and I saw people walking by and I was
I kind of hidden aside there and did it on purpose and this black lady looks up like what and I'm like
I'm just kidding. I just wanted to see you look up here. Ah, you got him. You got him mini. You got him. I
Did it with white people too. They got more offended
the
Yeah
Because remember when you went to go hang out with Marty and Jamie it looks like you yeah
They came over here, and we went to the
Barred the closest part at this karaoke, and I did a song for them and
That place is so packed they don't let me sing one song
So I came over here and performed in my apartment for him again
Marty already told me about he said you had a really cool apartment
Wow cool. Yeah, and he bought this cane from me. He started spinning the cane around and he broke it
So I crazy glued it for him. So I said here. Just let me fix it and then I I hit it
So I said you get it when you leave
There's this guy Casey and yeah, he's another one of those losers you just stay away from that, you know
We're trying to take a career, which is impossible, but you need to be aware of your career
He's gonna have your own career. Yeah, they're just really strange
Nobody can ever take anything from you. I agree. I agree. So yeah, KZ and Jay Dogger both losers
That's really I wanted to say you guys have a good rest of your stream and many was always good seeing
Thank you
Yeah, let me see if I okay
Yeah, I got pages in the chat pages in the chat to a page wants to come up because remember page pages loved your your lipstick game
Your lipstick you had the way you do your lipstick that night the blacks with the black lipstick
She's like oh, I love your I gotta get some more than I'm in trouble finding it
I'm gonna have to order it online if I don't find it here
There we got people that want to come say hi to you now
Sit say hello to many if say if mini says I can have you backed up
It's a I will but you know the same thing is the one we kicked off earlier
He's trying to come back and I think maybe apologize. I mean it can thumbs up sick apologize
Look at that when I was looking at right now. Oh my gosh. It's beautiful. I
Gotta show you
See it
Yeah
The flowers in my phone gets really hot when I fell my worry about that but the phone burns out and you don't see me anymore
That's why I have to get a new phone
Yeah, it's from the trees. It's from over there. I love trees in nature. This is what my block looks like
lovely
It's really nice
That's behind me right there, you know, so yeah
Great strong do great. I like that. Oh that brick work on the Porsche
Now you're gonna like this too
They did this last year
To the ceiling. Oh, yeah, it's wooden
Yeah, I'm not done reading that shit yet y'all
It was just the grass like for a month, I thought it was some kind of pod and it turned out it was a gnome statue
You thought I was a Norm's no sassy. Yeah, I know wherever you were too. Yeah, no
Garden gnome, but we have we have 48 people in the chat right now. We're talking about a lot of people in your chat
I noticed that
Yeah, well, I think they're here to see you today
Well, I don't want to suddenly blind anyone. So I covered that look at that there. I got that
Welcome to the disco. I love that. It is for the decorations. I was putting up
I don't want to dox myself. Let me see here. You should be able to see this new here. I saw Snoopy. Yep
We saw Snoopy
Snoopy oh
Nicola Christmas hat snoopy and snoopy and would suck I left it up because I liked it so much, but I have put up the
4th of July summer shit
Uh-huh, I like it. Yeah
Very patriotic and people know where I live and shit for why tell the world, huh?
Yeah, I know well my you know, I've I've gotten pizza sent to my house
I think one time seven times in a day the other day a couple times
If they're not paid for unfortunately, and so I just had to say it's just you you should just buy one of them
Yeah
Nick, if someone sent me a pizza and it was cheese, I'd pay for it.
I would.
We're having a kitty ray right now?
But if I have stuff like pepperonis and shit, I won't eat that.
No tuna either, even though that's a good idea.
Was there a great flood in Chicago or was it a great fire or was there both?
There was both. 1991, I think, or 1990 was when we had the flood.
under the city, because you know, there's a city under the city, and I'll let blooded, when somebody hit a pylon in the river, and it went.
Hi, Peter.
Hello.
Many, many, listen, I'm not talking to the psyche anymore. I don't want to talk to them. So, can you follow my son? Hi.
She said hi.
I heard her. I heard her. Thank you, Minnie. I'm really mad at you. Minnie, you backstabbed me on the back with like several swords and like, me and you like, you know, we had like, I was on your panel and I think you're fucking cool. And maybe you can like, knock some sense into his fucking head and tell him to stop being a backstabber to beat us kiddies.
stop doing that. Okay, there you go. Just do it. Just do it like from the kindness of your heart because Mini, I support you. I like you.
Thank you. I like hearing that.
Mini loves you.
Yeah.
Mini does still do art.
Can you tell Saiki I love how Mini?
Okay
Can you tell you tell me that I love her too and we're gonna work this all out cuz we're
Mad at someone and then the next day it's okay
I heard what you said
You can rewind it later and you'll hear it.
No, he just said it because I forced it upon him, you know.
It was a forceful, I made you say that.
Because, you know, you're in shit.
Minnie understands me and Psyche does that.
How the fuck did I communicate with you Psyche?
And Minnie understands me better than Psyche.
I'm going to get a tattoo of you on my heart.
Yeah, get a tattoo of Minnie Manson.
I'm going to get a little Minnie tattoo of you on my heart.
I want to get a tattoo when you get it.
I do like Minnie Manson, but I like...
I like Minnie Manson, I like Marilyn Manson,
but I like Nine Inch Nails,
so should I get one of Trent Reznor?
Like a little miniature...
What do you call it?
... of Trent Reznor on my chest.
You can get them get one of many Manson like my avatar like this logo here. Look on the screen. You see that
But I have a cartoon
This one
So you have one. I like it. I like it. I like it. I don't have any tattoos. Yeah, my first tattoo will be the mini mountain tattoo
sakey, please don't I get jealous because
Everybody should get a tattoo of many
Tattoo ever and it's gonna be right on my heart. So of who?
Shout out to you, mini
Okay
Yeah of you
She's gonna get a tattoo of you mini. I know that's hot
I'd rather I'd rather get a beautiful tattoo of you than on psyche
and
I'm just trying to make a statement here a statement to say that psyche has not been loyal loyal
He doesn't love me and I'm gonna get a little mini
Tiny little one cuz I'm a pussy. I'm gonna take a little one
I've never had a tattoo before of mini Manson on my heart before I have one of psyche
Thank you. What do you think about that?
I think it's awesome and hot.
I think so too many
where are you going to put the tattoo
on my
it's my heart
but I mean it's not going to be like
I'm like
it'll be like you know I'll show it to you later
your heart is actually
the freak off they're happening later baby
actually your heart is like right there
just left the center in the middle
so yeah like on your
no higher higher
like higher
Yeah, right there. So I don't I don't want to hide it. I want everybody in the world to see it. Fuck. Yeah
Anyways, I'll be back. I'm like really glad that you're up here. I love to see him happy
I love your smiling face, but I'm still mad at him and tell him I said goodbye
Wish you a good bye
She loves you. Thank you. Thank you, Minnie. Bye. Bye for now. Bye for now, Bita. Bye for now
I'm helping you make peace with a shitload of people
Yeah, I know you see this weirdo who walks up and down my street every day. He looks like Jeffrey Dahmer
and John Wayne Gacy and a bunch of other serial killers rolled in the one I
Don't care who you kill. Just stay on your own property
Oh, you can murder up the whole neighborhood. Just not me
That's what my for
My one of my first shows I started going on they're like you look like Jeffrey Dahmer to me and I have these Dahmer glass
I don't know if I around you should go about a click the clear ones like
Barbara's son when he was younger when he used to slay the babes
He had these glasses that were clear and they look like Dahmer glasses. Oh
I can't see up the lower your head a little more
I
later on as he got older turn into a babe machine
We have another guest
I do many Ross videos and I do my artwork I
Have videos tonight, so I won't be able to go live tonight
That a case he wants to meet you mini man, sir. All right, come on up
Hey, many of you right now. How are you? I'm okay
Very cool
Nice to nice to meet you. I've heard of you. Never never met you though
I'm usually so busy, but I saw
Have some few hours to hang out and relax out here. So I thought I'll come out very cool
I remember first seeing you on Alicia Giudana. Oh, yeah, I moved her
I was
I remember that that's
Into the soul not the closest in the sex that Elise will ever have
Well, I don't know like Lisa's dated some you know
Benji and Andy dick and captain content. I trolled Andy dick, and then I blocked them. She's still
content too
I'm like get out of here asshole. I bet I bet Andy like you man. He wanted to do it with me and I'm like, you know, get out of here. Oh, yeah
Not interested
He's not even protected by Hollywood anymore. He's like all the riffraff. He got to walk down the street like all the other losers
He's yeah
Billy John was helping in my last last time it was Billy John
I don't have to lay a finger on him to destroy him. All I have to do is just remind him that he's an outsider in Hollywood
Is that what the people in Hollywood get?
Is that what the people, is that what you people in Hollywood get? Limousines? Limousines, Champagne, Corbell is my favorite
Oh man
They used to Corbell that TV show Combat
That was on in the late 60s
They used to film a lot of their episodes at the winery and pretend it was France
So I kind of like that company I
Can't believe when I see it like this. This is disturbing
And you never really know what the story is behind families
But they're claiming that Carol Burnett abandoned her
Grants son and he's homeless in a wheelchair. I don't like to hear about people being homeless
And being attacked by other people and being at risk like that. I
Hate hearing that shit
Right I heard a similar story of a Warren Buffett
He has a granddaughter and he and he like cut his granddaughter out of his will
Hey one second
Who is the woman that played Dorothy on Wizard of Oz?
Hey, Minnie.
That's another guy.
That's Judy Garland.
Quick question for Minnie.
Yeah, Judy Garland had a lot of problems.
Didn't she?
Christ.
KZ.
Hey, Minnie, real quick.
You heard the term locale before.
Right?
Yeah.
Unfortunately, that's what KZ, if he was a little more interesting, that's what he
would be.
But really, he's quite a bore.
that's why everyone tries to stay away from KZ. He brings that energy with him.
He's a weirdo is my point. You're you're he's way beneath you mini. Yeah, that's true
It's absolutely
Whoever that is
a peon
Most people are
Yeah, next in chess is on keys. He is a slow cow, which means you know, he's not yeah
Yeah
Yeah, he's the weird one, this guy.
We get it, right?
Right, many we get it.
Yeah, you get it, wake, wake.
So KZ got himself a new mic.
You got a new mic, KZ.
You still sound a little slow. Yeah. Well, no, I but I do you're horrible to listen to
Horrible it's gonna clip right to my hat. I'm gonna be any much easier. You sound retarded, sir
It's not like any commands the microphone mini commands the microphone KZ. You're just dull. You're a bore
Yeah, you can smell the retard on this guy. I'm sure of it. I'm sure of it
I don't know. I'm not well to be honest. I just
You don't know these things and you know, I thought it would be the polite thing to do is to tell you, you know
Oh, Indiana Jones
Oh, hell, yeah, hell. Yeah, mini
Yeah
And uh, nick johnson, uh posted mini mansons cash app in chat
Uh, if you do send mini manson a cash app be sure to write the comments. KZ is a retard
Well, let's get let's get mini some dough knows for KZB to retire
Sometimes you
With the Hollywood gossip, what was his name with the Hollywood
He was on Howard Stern every Friday. They did the
His name is my his name is Mike something
Insight KZ such incredible insight. Yeah
Please tell us more
of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of all of
Indiana Jones role was considered, they were gonna consider Steven Spielberg told on Nick Mancusa
You're too ethnic for the role because he's too Sicilian and Italian
He's actually from Calabria
Yeah, he's a cool actor that I used to like so much. I still like him. Yeah, that's good to know good
No being an actor. I still like him though. His movies are cool
We had an acting school and everything and I wanted to I was gonna go to it
But then he got sick and he couldn't do it and then COVID happen
You thought about expanding your talents to acting to yeah
So I studied acting in theater and all that stuff
Acting drawing anything with the arts. I took in college. I graduated from college bats or birds
Now KZ couldn't act he's too retarded. I would love to understand when he talks many you could barely understand the man
He shouldn't be on a microphone really
It's insulting to talents like you that Kaysie's even a lot up here to be quite honest
See you get it. Many gets it everybody. All right. I'm gonna drop psyche
You and Minnie have a great rest of your stream. Don't let losers like Kaysie fuck it up for you
Mumble it all over the place. Take care of me. You roll
Thanks, that's hot and liking all this fan warship. Many Manson likes it when you idolize him
I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't know what I'm talking about, but I don't
The word search I love that word screen shot of this and then later you can do this puzzle. Oh, yeah, there you go. Yeah
That's for you guys
Very cool. Okay, you said again, you'll be able to get a screenshot. I held it up long enough
Yeah
Not like any old TV shows really hold something up for five minutes
You can sit there and read it nowadays. They just flash it once and then they say go back
I'd pause it and then look at it.
And that's when you find all the Easter eggs and shit in TV shows.
Right.
Yeah.
Minnie, can I ask you a question?
Sure.
I'm actually subbed to you and I remember I saw you had posted a video about you were gonna confront some guy who was bullying you at the local
Store or something. Oh, no, it was bully. Yeah, I was bullying me for like six months
So I went in with my camera and I said hey this shit stops and you know that he doesn't bully me anymore after that
I only had to go once I should stop because I have fans and they will come here and they will
Call the store and they will get you fired if you don't leave me alone as a guy was like six is like 70 tall it literally
Yeah, I saw that when you did I saw that video when you did it long
Yeah, I've deleted it because this woman said I would call the store. I called the police
This lady claims she's
Never
Just says she still cares about me so I made peace with her and all but it's a please don't call people on me because
I'm already poor and my
quality of life is very limited and
If you're calling the stores around me, I can't function. I can't buy food even
That's that and they're saying a shoplifting shit. She's like, I'm telling you please don't tell if you're not gonna give me money
To buy shit that I need don't tell on me. I just won't talk about it no more as all
Yeah
Okay, people like to get in other people's business and yeah
comfortable around that
Yeah
A lot of people don't understand about being poor and having to survive and I'll do what it takes to survive
Help I knew how to steal a house. I would do it
Some people are smart they know how to get pretty shit like that houses and cars. I'm not that smart
Well, it's always
There's a lot of legitimate ways to get those things for free and so yeah, yeah
Right up. Oh
Yeah, that's the only interesting couple. I like Barack Obama. He's cool
There's a reason I got this voucher. I gotta give him credit
Is that okay? Oh, I don't know what that is that you guys can do this too
Domino's okay. I know how to do that. I
Like to play real dominoes. I used to when I went through Miami
Dorito got lodged in there, okay
Then I used to go to Miami when I went to the airport one time when I was waiting for the Greyhound boss
It wasn't gonna leave for like
the
Yeah, they're crazy bird. Well, actually there's something called primal astrology. You just you mix your your sun sign with
With the Chinese sign and it comes up with another animal
And so for a Capricorn monkey Capricorn monkey is called
Your capricorn
Yeah, mr. Capricorn hi
Give another guess that what's this a high you're leaders they stand on the top
It's like a wheel, but that's all like
Zodiacs and Capricorns on the top and the leadership Marilyn Manson is also a capricorn
Yeah, he's I think he's January 5th. I'm January 7th. So we're like
Within that couple days. Hey, hey, hey, say hi. Hi
Hello, it's nice to meet you again many thank you
Yes, well, I guess it's like the third time. I think I've met you now
So I'm not really meeting you so just hello
Page is a fan page page is the one that said I like your makeup game. I love or your your lips your lipstick
Yeah, you're fucking lip liners on point
Love the black lips. I'm a big fan
Sorry about that
Okay
When it comes out and it looks like a tree trunk when I put it real close like that
Cash shop is many man's and talent. So is my PayPal but I also don't know and tell
Have a lot of mirth and I could do a song I'm filming some song videos tonight
You guys want to send me $30? I'll do a video for you. Just make sure there's a karaoke version of the song
I can follow through and I'll do a song for you tonight.
Minnie, how's your coloring book coming along?
That's also coming along good.
That's going to be $30.
They're going to be very thick pages.
Nice.
Cardstock, there's only going to be one design
and one side of the page so you can take them out
and put them up when you are done coloring them.
There'll be about 52 pages to it.
You get two free stickers included with it.
A big one and a little one
Uh-huh. It's really cool
Good job, could you could you perform a song like two pox hit them up? I
Don't have my
I'm outside. I don't have my I'm saying I'm saying like if somebody paid 30 bucks for it like what what song?
Two pock hit them up. You've never heard of that my best
if
I'll do two pocket if you send me $30. I'll do the video guys. We guys don't get cancer me right now
I gotta do videos
Don't get gangster before I get gangster. Hold on. Maybe nine o'clock my time. Chicago time
Right now it's 421 here mini. Hold on. I I gotta confess something before psyche like kills me
Um, I wanted to block arthur, but I don't know if I banned him or I blocked him. That's all I wanted to say mini
Which I'm a bad somebody I wanted to block him so I don't see his stupid face like
Yeah
Listen mini mini mini I was in the chat. I didn't want to see his disgusting face. So I
Wanted to not see it. Yeah, I want to block
But I didn't know if I bad him or not, but then oh my god, look at this hotty. Oh my god
That's my man, that's my ex blue. He broke up
Hello, I think someone
Really cute though, like he's really hot
You're a very good looking guy blogger
Get a roll don't throw your hair like that. It makes me know
Ready for the freak off
No, but maybe don't you think like blogger is cute. He's a cute guy or am I wrong?
Give me some.
I can't even see him.
There you go.
Hold on.
I'm on my phone.
I can't.
Oh, look at him.
You can't hold beautiful skinny.
He's so cute.
Look at his hair.
I suppose he's okay.
Bita, thank you.
He's okay?
I think he's cute.
I've got a different taste in guys.
But I suppose he's okay.
Well, I get you.
Yeah, Bita.
You changed my mind.
I appreciate the compliment, Bita.
That's very nice of you.
I tell you, you're good-looking because you are, but you're mean about my eyebrows.
No, and actually yeah, I was gonna tell you a little tiny guy page. I was just joking you you know what I mean?
I was just kidding there tonight, so don't he's gonna kind of take blogger away from me. I know you're pretty
You may be younger and prettier, but I got that Persian spell
Don't even start that
Yeah, so many verified that blogger is cute chill. All right. I'm good
This is turning really odd um, but no, what's going on blog? Oh, wait
My heart my heart does kind of want to be that I will say oh my god
I was just saying so like page page of the way you're trying to move in like that like
Don't leave her hanging don't gang up on me you fucking asshole. I won't now leave him hanging
I'll keep him on top of his fucking tree. Oh, like he'll be you know, he won't be hanging
He will never be hanging. It'll be good
No, I
Baked power couple again. We starting our eBay store up again after four years
Yeah, we're gonna finally we're gonna finally log off and like get to work one of these days
We'll stop joining the panels and actually
Love story. It's a love. Yeah
Me me. I love you too. It's so cute
See at least many a copy for us blogger seems very jealous of the situation. Oh, wait, what I'm jealous
Yeah
But I'm being respectful. I'm being respectful to psych. I'm not gonna say anything
Uh psych thank you, uh, so did Tracy forgive you? I just like I started watching beat a stream, but then I fell asleep
It was kind of
Yeah, she did what a compliment blogger
No, I'm sorry, I wasn't trying to fall asleep. Yeah, um, okay. I was just wondering
We're all good. We're all good.
No, we're not all good.
We're not all good.
Are we chat?
Some people in chat are cool with psych,
but other people are not very cool
with the way you've handled things,
but I mean...
Handle things?
Like I gave a full refund,
I chose with friends, you know.
Yeah, so like yeah, I just said we made a mistake psyche today doesn't mean you've been all like angels, you know
I mean, I mean, let's just get over it till the next time till you fuck me over again. You call me a bit
See what be the things in her head. That's what a lot of people think of you now psych because you've made people
I can guess you
Well, it's okay. You get to know me you get to know me
Then you'll know the real person if you're just gonna base it on what other people are saying and
But I will be
Just join join the hate train join the hate train
Here's the thing you say join the hate train like you had
All quiet on the Western front, you know, I found it for free in one of those book notes
Looks pretty freaking cool off the book. I would it's not what you find every day
So he's all mad because he doesn't like he acts like it's like he this shit's just happening to him
Like he just hit live. He's he's just some innocent guy trying to have a tarot channel and doing the day doing his best
And then not the right attack
Just just all out of nowhere all these people are just going against you
But really do you think you are any part of the common denominator and some of these complaints?
There's just everybody going crazy just
Uh what happened was like psyche decided to ghost me for four days
So if he would have kept contact with me it would all been like, you know cleared up
But he didn't know what he's doing because he's a dingbat and he's a rookie and he's like kind of I don't know
He might be brunette, but he's probably stupid and blonde and he decided to sleep and drink it off
And like not like clarify where he sends the cash off the extra 30, you know
And okay, can I say something like 28 hours and 25 fucking days and he was Alex back
Alexander's NYPD guy and I'd rather have Minnie Manson up here
Who's a fucking true gangster celebrity musician and a rock star over some yappity yapp?
Like Alexander and he's still not smiling because Minnie is up here. You should be smiling. That's hot
Yeah, I mean Alex is not a great panel guest whatsoever. I don't think I haven't seen him add anything to a panel ever
But yeah, but we got content. Many knows how to fucking do this shit. Hell yeah, I mean
You got this of hot even when I'm really like that's my little Paris Hilton's when the Persian Riz
Well, would you rather have many Manson or Alex? Come on, Paige. You give me your... Come on. Be honest. Just like, don't be a Canadian. Don't be Switzerland. Don't be neutral.
What do you want? Mini or Alex? If you have to choose right now. You can't say, I don't know. Just say one.
Awesome.
I'm a blogger.
I'm an entertainer.
Yeah, blogger.
Have you met Minnie Manson?
Say hello to Minnie Manson.
Hello, Minnie Manson.
Actually, I've seen Minnie Manson.
I think I saw Minnie Manson a couple of years ago on something.
I think, yeah, something related to Alisa when Alisa was on IP2.
Yeah.
Nice to meet you.
Hey.
I'm still your favorite rockstar
Stopped a mini Manson just type in mini Manson. I was a little over 3,000 subs. That's me
I'm already subbed to you bitch, okay
Make five other like a
cute-ass mini
Cool FedEx is here. Fuck. Yeah
I
Got a size of that truck
Are you talking about bloggers penis
Well, that's kidding. I'm just I didn't know
Shut the fuck up. I get distracted very easily. I have ADHD you guys. I'm sorry
I'll put myself on mute
You have to pay stuff
Hey Manson you're welcome, buddy. I'm the reason all these people are here
Awesome shine like the sunshine you are buddy. You got it, buddy
Many do not be fooled by that that one. I'm the reason
I'm the reason that I'm here when I saw many here
I said I'm gonna get a tattoo and when I get that little mini mini tiny tattoo
It's gonna be very small. It might be a little dot, but it's gonna be just for you
Now for me
All right, well, I'm gonna get a tattoo for you like a BKG tattoo under my armpit
We're gonna have a break off party everybody get a mini tattoo
That's why I did the artwork of my logo so you could get tattoos with it
Okay, mommy can I get a tattoo of you on my face?
What the fuck did I just say?
Bita wants the sandwich between Minnie and Lager to make Psych jealous.
Oh, yeah.
I don't want to make Psych jealous.
Psych is already jealous.
That's what blue, blue.
There's enough Minnie for all of you jealous.
Like he's jealous by default.
Anyhow, maybe I can make a circle in the middle and put me in there.
And then you can also round me.
Minnie, Psych is doomed for life.
He got a tattoo and he's doomed for life.
He's going to have to change it to big.
Manchin. No. Manchin. No, it's a big mansion because that's what you're going to have in the future.
I'm manifesting mansions. You're a mansion. I need to manifest that.
Yes, you're a mini mansion. You're my mini mansion.
My mansion, my limousine, my champagne, pink champagne.
I'm gonna get your chauffeur. It's gonna be like a freaking like Rolls Royce like phantom
Yeah
Are you my employers will be wearing black suits with either a black shirt or a white shirt
I you know they're gonna be professional looking
Yes, mm-hmm. We're gonna get psyche a little Kia like a little fucking cheap Kia. You know, have you seen those cars?
It's like worse than like a fucking spy on I think you should get a Ford Pinto
Remember in the 70s
Pinto is from the 1970s
Butterfly would land in a bumper and it would go boom
Well, that was a job because they were very
Volatile why hold on why the hell would psych even need a car
He just needs to get to the like from his house to the taco place
So he just seems like a moped basically
He's a car so you can drive to electric scooter and beat my electric scooter, right?
I'm getting an e-bike. I'm getting out or a e-bike
Many Manson are you on many Manson young oblox? What's going on? Are you like are you in the shy?
What's all block? I don't want to dock you by you and are you in shy town right now? Are you?
I know I knew
I rack out there. All right
Good
IRL
Jeffrey Dahmer, I don't know if you could see that because it's so hard to see on here
I can't turn the camera around. It's actually really really good
Actually, the neighborhood kind of reminds me of Washington DC. I I was in DC a couple times and I do it looks like Jeffrey Dahmer
I went through some like distinguished black nipples.
Just like mini mini go up to him just as a joke him just like just like don't even just be like
Wait, I'm I'm expecting a package of this for me. Let's give like some interaction
We won't say don't guys don't say nothing
Don't mess with the FedEx guy.
Just be like, is this my package?
No, I'm not going up to him.
I'm gonna get in his business.
I'm trying to teach Nike how to IRL.
He doesn't know how to do it.
Well, messing around with someone who lives on my block
isn't the right idea.
Oh, you might be right.
If you are one of the neighbors and expecting a package,
I am expecting a package.
Well, then it could be yours.
What are you expecting?
My God.
Don't say that.
the
Oh shit, I'm gonna leave by mini. I'm not getting a tattoo. No mini. I'm done with you. No no tattoo for you
Me just call me the n-word I'm gonna put the n-word with a dot
You better be joking
What just happened many I'm getting a tattoo of my I'm getting a tattoo a little mini with a little and
And that says
Don't worry. I won't stand up. We're no more psyche. I'm sorry. All right. All right. What are you gonna apologize to me?
Are you gonna apologize to me? You call me that word though. I know I was messing around too.
Hey, come on. Come on. Go nini nini on you little mini. Thank you. Say it.
Cause actually, mini, I thought you're gonna get offended by, I thought you're gonna be offended by psych earlier for him. We're not like sick.
Sick was messing around talking about the n-word or something and not yeah, I don't get offended
That's why I said it as soon as I said it all all the trolls quit picking on me
I don't I'm gonna subscribe. I don't like you leave that. I don't
No, no, no, mini no more. No, that's that's cool though. That's cool. My you broke my heart many
little mini versions. Do you say it? We're not going to let me just say I'm sorry and I'll forgive
you in a little bit. Stop being so starstruck right now. Let mini talk. Mini just broke my heart
though. I was going to get a tattoo. I'm starstruck by a mini guy like he's so cute. You're going to
be careful about that stuff.
About being starstruck. You call me that you call me that any
body
I just said uh
Just go press the fedex guy though. Oh, you wanted me to talk to the fedex guy now and you call me a
Oh, let's understand you the fedex guy was hot but that guy walking by was disgusting. Can I get a kiss and apologize?
Yeah, i'm sorry
Oh, okay. I give it. I grabbed. Thank you. Thanks. That's a little open
Thank you all understanding humor. I do have
You know bloggers are very jealous man. No, I was literally just sitting here. I'm engaging. I'm engaging with Minnie
You guys don't know how to interview and engage with Minnie. I'm doing the Minnie
I was just standing here thinking like even though you're kind of fangirling out I'm going to go cray
Shut the fuck up blogger. You don't know how to do the Minnie verse. You're like you're just a big verse
You don't know the mini verse. I still support BKG. Okay, you can do what you do
My phone is at like 50% so I can be out here for like about 10 more minutes.
I have seven percent.
I don't want to overstay my welcome either. If I'm ending her too long I get
Literally like I would just leave ever
If you leave I'll I'll unsubscribe to psyche it all depends on you now
It's all on your shoulders
Well, I can stay for about 10 more minutes and then I have to go relax because it's night after work
You guys if many if many leaves everybody unsubscribe to psyche's channel
It's called peer pressure because I wouldn't come back on
Don't pull down your pants just be like just I'm not I was just kidding. I'm fixing the waistband because it's hurting my belly
Oh my god, mini just farm bomb the oh
I have my clothes is on my clothes is
That's okay. You can take it off, but not now. We'll take it. I
Studied you before I thought you wanted me to go talk to the neighbor and not to the bed ex guy
And I'm like I'm gonna mess with my neighbors. I would have went up in a bed ex guy, but understood you
You're absolutely saucy and amazing I love to just joke around with you because you're
I was thinking like you could just ask him like hey, I'm expecting a package to not a gun like by the way
I know and then you say I wasn't
Yeah, it's like I can't wait. I want my dildos go bad and then you know it would have been great content
Oh shit, he's gonna do it. Don't do it mini. I stopped it. I was just kidding with you mini. I know don't do that
But it would be great if you just go up to him and you're like when he already left you're like yeah
I'm expecting a package and he's like I can't wait for my dildo like my vibrator. I've been waiting
Yeah, butter put some respect on my boy mini Manson
I spent on you think I spent on you signal you are spit your spits come back
We're this is uh, oh my god, I'm giving fucking mini ahead. I gotta give them a back shoulder
rod. No, I'm stretching because I need to. Just like a little mini bear, my little mini bear,
mini teddy bear. Oh my god, is he doing the mini teddy bear stretch?
Like he, do you want me to leave?
Don't leave me. No, don't leave. Um, I'll be right back. I'm just touching my neck
My neck my back everything on my crack my neck
Sounds like he's so quiet I can flirt with you mini man son mini
Why is like why is psych such a fucking like prissy bitch? Have you ever heard of that? Like he's a prissy bitch
I'm like he's a prissy bitch to buy an ice cream cone
There's an ice cream truck coming
You know, you know how to do IRL, but thank you doesn't know how to do IRL like you
Do I have any money left? Oh fuck I do
Of course you do you're rich and we're
Manifestation home. Uh-huh. Well, I suppose I'm rich because I live in the USA. So, yeah
If the ice cream truck comes down here now, I can buy ice cream
Who just coughed like that was that J-Doc
No, no J-Doc should go J-Doc should go
J-Doc was kidding with you
Look, I drew the kiss logo on this
Guess logo
I mean you're so cute
Thank you. Yeah, would you get jealous if I take me off of your hands?
What I'll just jump on top of them and cuddle him. He's gonna be my new spoon cuddle buddy
We can cuddle together. You're no longer. You're too skinny to be my cuddle buddy psyche. I need like a real cuddly guy
He likes to be in the sun he gets out
He's an artist. He takes a break two days or three days before he comes on the platform
And then he savers a moment and he starts like a fucking he's like a shining star. Look at that man
I'm gonna get a tattoo of the mini on me
I'm going to do it. It's going to be really small though. It's going to be tiny because I'm a pussy. It's going to be
You have a question for many or should I just like just continue to
Savor the moment with me to do that
Yeah, we'll save her in the moment
Savor the moment, okay
These are the moments that make life worth living
What would you do without what would you do say what would you do say key without me and mini and blogger on your panel?
You would just be a boring ass to our car reader. Yeah, he doesn't even read tarot. He doesn't read tarot
He just looks at the chat and waits for
Oh, you you bring him back you drop blogger off
Yeah, oh you bring them back now before I like jump off to and then
And then I can't jump on top of a Mickey mini mini bring bliggy
Bliggy come back
Stop it bring blogger see it's like you don't like anybody's opinion to like
Me and mini we're cuddling and we're savoring the moment and you got jealous of blogger
God answer shit down here. You're lucky. No, don't they ask him bite like they can bite and it's not these ants I
Don't live in the south. I live up north
It's beautiful where you love
I can take a dick I can take a joke so I took a dick and I took a joke why can't you take
Because he's not joking, it's not funny.
He is, he's joking and you can take a dick, so take it one at a time.
The joke is usually something that I would say, uh-huh, like or like, you know, instead of saying, oh, it's just feels like an insult
And it's just all right. Don't get something up. Oh, thank you. I love you. I'll get a mini tattoo of you
Psycho mini-tatcher. Are you 45 or younger? I can't I think you're 45 once
Me me looks like he's like
Me me like
The reason I ask it's like I feel like the generation kind of mini is gonna bite me and I'm gonna be a vampire too
Many how do I like come into the vampire game?
This is how he's getting his son he's a vampire he needs to get a little bit of daylight
He's a vampire you guys just look at me and get a little bit of vampire son
He just looks like he's just like a little bat right now back all
I call that shmackles
That bitch be coming soon
Let's do the Tommy
Tommy's doing his impression of a gay painter right now. I like it
Oh shit, the ice cream truck's getting closer.
Oh shit, I'm in heaven, I'm in heaven.
I got Tommy, I got fucking Katie, I got Locker, I got Psyche.
I don't give two fucks about KZ, KZ can't kick her off.
He better come down the street, that's what I got.
KZ, no, don't unmute yourself, we don't care.
Oh fuck no, he's running around the corner there.
Shut up KZ, I was like, I was favoring the moment.
Are you fucking adding anything to the panel at all?
I'm sorry KZ you can mute yourself kids by the school Mr. Ice Cream truck. Why'd you go away? I?
Was gonna buy ice cream you went around the corner there
Getting a better mic
No, I can't buy ice cream. I'm sad now. I
Swear to God better Mike Casey like talks into like a corner. I have a new my
I'll show you my mind. I'll show you my Mike. I'll show you my Mike
I'll show you my mic, Minnie.
It's really small though, I'm a woman.
I think me and Minnie could actually hang out.
I think me and Minnie could actually have a full night
of just killing me and Jamie Rose.
Me and Jamie Rose are a fucking peep.
Can me and Minnie hang out too?
I really want to hang out.
VV and Chad, I just turned 30 actually.
I just turned 30. Yeah, shut the fuck up blogger. Don't make me look like
I used to but I don't need more than this is I'm older so they're just kind of sparse now
If I could grow mustache I would
If I would have, if I would have, just to start, just to start.
I would have though he would look actually pretty amazing
Tommy can you put your parcel like the one with your head learn mustache for a minute? I love that
That's like how does he ever been in your life?
You look so good in that picture you look so hot you were just the top like
Remember that one with the red jacket with the that one you look so fucking good in that picture
I'm a weird for liking that picture Tommy. I like you I like you
but the bohemian librarian poetry look where I'm just a stoner I'm just gonna
kill is not like your look I like you know our Tommy we like our Tommy and
You know
Tommy's trying to bring a distinguished like
You're going all black on I want to thank I want to thank psych for being like so repulsive for actually
No
Blogger strike blogger strike
I'll go live right now psyche and mini Manson is gonna come on my panel
I'm gonna get a mini tattoo
I'm gonna have a mini channel and Tommy is gonna be my mini like bring blogger back. Please
He just called me repulsive on my own show and then
Joe he didn't say anything against your
Don't be don't be like a little snowflake. Don't be our snowflake bring him back. Oh
He just bring yourself back
Bring both of you guys. Oh, he went he went backstage with blogger. Oh my god, Tommy him and blogger are having a free party right now
Tommy I do you see what's happening?
Tommy yeah, they went backstage though
Well, that's beautiful many freaks. They won't act in the backstage just
others
Yeah
Bring blogger back. I don't want him to get e violated by your e-dick right now. Thank you
Yeah, bring your e ass back up back
Thank you, you got mini math on your favorite on the panel don't leave
Get your E. Okay. Well, I won't say what I'm thinking, but I was trying to make a joke, but it was kind of
Nothing, he's
There's actually some realism to my joke, but
Okay, um, so yeah
Like he was like being so mean like he come back don't be a bitch. I'll call you bitch again bitch
the first time I met that psych dude he played like some weird game with me remember he like left
he's like i'll just go i'll just leave i'll leave and then he left you know what he had to go leave
probably to get more alcohol it's okay he's just making an excuse i know i excuse the people
You know how we know it cuz if he was really here he would join
Yeah, he would join and he would put like mini on the big screen
He left to blend and to get more beer. He manipulated all of us and
Yeah, don't worry about it. Well, good now that we have his panel. We can see whatever we want
You'll probably get my phone, my phone's a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale, I'll have to use it only when my phone is a phone for sale,
Okay, I gotta go charge it again. I love you. I gotta rest up to work tonight. You bring sunshine to my world. Yeah
Many don't leave me ever
Many
I'm in love with mini you guys
Actually, mini man's was actually kind of was cool. He's fucking cool as fuck
I would have expected them to be honestly not for free speech and they were so like that was something I was
I didn't mean it was like a sweetie. Yeah, I was just being narrow-minded. I guess I don't know
But once I said once I said the n-word I was like wow
He didn't he really just said it like slightly like he just a mini. He said a mini and he was like a lower capital case
There you go free speech Tommy what's going on with your look these days? What's up with your glasses your hardcore like
That's the only thing that I miss the days when you was tripping dance and just go like juggalo for us
Good juggalo for us
I don't know if that's gonna happen like you want right now be the crazy. What do you have to add? How you do?
Be thanks for trying to draw me into my back Maya fucking dark Tommy
I always told you when you grow your back below you get that hard fucking shit rocked up
I got shit lined up for you not not pussy. No, not pussy. No
You've got a lot of opportunities because I think you're absolutely an amazing person you're an artist and
your hard worker you got potentials and I told you that like what nine months ago
get your shit cleared out and I'll get you a solid job that will get you what seven eight
thousand dollars commission minimum I don't lie I can do that and a lot of people like how you're
What about me? I'm kind of a salesman.
You're you're definitely like me or me and you have no patience for that shit.
This guy does. He's this guy.
Tommy will tolerate it.
Me and you will flip off.
We'll just go crazy.
We need to be our own business woman and I put up with a lot of shit.
Honestly, Tommy has to work for somebody else.
Tommy is an artist.
Meanwhile, he has to work for somebody else and make good money
till he gets what he wants.
Me and you will never.
We just we got a hustle and be our own business woman and men
You know, I think in this day and age you got to have both like a regular job in the hustle, I guess, you know
That's why like my chatterbait is like really on the up
Yeah, can we get a can we get a Tommy and um vlogger collab in real life one day?
It wouldn't be that hard it wouldn't be that hard to do it wouldn't be that hard to do
I'll be like I'll just control you both. I'll get the pepper spray and the bug spray. I mean I'll get it ready
I'll talk. I think we could do
that to you guys. I think Tommy
and blogger can have a
friendship again. That's what it
would take is me getting sent
a song. And I jump. Tommy, can
I ask you a question? Yeah.
I am can I are you just going to be uptight like you got a dildo up your ass right now?
Okay, all right. I'm just wondering
I mean
I don't want to like bore the whole panel about your uptightness asshole because I can ask blogger first the same question
I'm doing an interview
When you did meet up with blogger when you did meet up with blogger
all jokes aside what was like the funnest like part of the whole thing not not
the not the shit shit like what was like fun part about you guys what it was like
the funnest thing when you and vlogger at that moment were you like actually I'm
having a I'm having fun with this guy
When he fed me drugs
No, I didn't say he's thank you, but when you met him did you actually enjoy like a moment where you guys were like
Actually
What was the highlight of the fun
can i say something to interlude uh i'm gonna ask you the same question blogger i think you
would okay all right all right go ahead um he's pondering like like tommy is pondering right
now see him he's like touching a beard thinking you don't have an answer all right so all right
blogger go ahead i think i'll say this i think a lot of
The potential between between like Tommy and myself got kind of fucked up from the start
I don't really feel as in the same. I'm definitely we're both not in the same places
We used to be but like a fun part for me was like basically the first time I went to go like collab with him
I guess like
Chat knew that was a possibility, but that was like me and him, right?
Absolutely, absolutely. The highlight was the excitement of just meeting up.
I love that answer, blogger. Thank you.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's pretty cool. I didn't get that. I get that.
Go on, blogger.
Even though I did tell him even though I try to like tell him
Act like I'm not here. Just be live for a little bit
I was trying to hang out in this garage and then I was gonna like walk into the stream
But he did like kind of give it up quick, but it's fine. I mean we have creative differences, which is
You know, it's part of the problem and it's also what makes it good. I guess. I don't know. Yeah, I respect that blogger
Thank you. That was a beautiful answer. There you go. There you go. There you go
Your turn homie, I thought I answered already. Yeah, literally said nothing you had nothing to say
Blogger like something that was really good
Listen, I can give you one moment, like, I mean, just give it, like, don't be prideful, don't be prideful, Ginger.
You know, you weren't listening. I said that my favorite part was when I did the drugs and when he fed the drugs into my mouth.
But that's really, that's almost like your, uh, blogger is not a human being. Blogger is not like drugs. Like what you just said was fucked up. Blogger is not drugs.
I feel it I feel it go go go like the IRL hype who loves it like you go beautiful man
Look at it. Look at it. Like he's like golden hair lock and that was one of my
Thank you. Um, blogger that was like, um, uh, I asked some stupid questions
sometimes just to open the door for how people's hearts are really at or.
How solid they are and that's all you know, Tommy you could have given me something you could have given me something
Drugs are good. What is what does drugs do drugs like like not me you they
I would ask about blogger not drugs
In my opinion, uh, it's a very touchy situation. I don't know. Fuck it
You're being like an asshole right now Tommy I asked about actually
And that's it the rest was not fun
Tommy why don't you take the blame for taking the drugs bitch
Listen Tommy, you're not gonna sit here and like act like you're silver and self-conscious all the sudden
I didn't ask you about drugs. I even eliminated that I said
What did you like about meeting up with blogger and you keep bringing up drugs?
You act like you never fucking did drugs before you met blogger. Oh blogger bought me the drugs for the first time in my life
I never did drugs in my life
Blogger blogger you introduced me to drugs forever
Let's no, let's yeah, because you're acting like a two-year-old. I asked you seven times
I did not
I asked you do you like anything about blogger?
Well, you said what was my favorite experience from hanging out with you.
Well, except the drug experience, you fucking drugie.
Listen, I will say Tommy James in my opinion has liked a lot about me
You want another fucking memory that's all I wanted was like another moment Tommy. I know like
We need you and like blogger whoever we're gonna do drugs we're gonna drink we're gonna smoke some pot
We are gonna I'm not talking about like
Here's the thing. Yeah, I want to know the summary. I want to know. I don't want to know a summary
I want to know the highlight. I want to know
I'm gonna go retry
Tommy, Tommy, if I met up with you,
we would probably smoke weed.
We'd probably do shrooms and probably smoke weed.
I'm not talking, I mean, like, I would do fucking awful.
I'm not talking about drugs.
I said, is there a moment where you,
what was it, where you met up?
You are the worst, you know, you don't,
I don't even want to interview you anymore.
You're stupid.
Thank you for being like an honest interviewee.
Tommy is like a jokester and a clown.
Read the room, read the card.
Ah, you want me to leave the room?
You said read the room or read the card.
Look at the chat.
The chat says that you're fucking like a self-righteous,
fucking like wannabe, silver motherfucker
who was fucking like dozing off a week ago.
Oh, yeah.
The room says that the room says that an addict cannot judge even if you go to AA and I'm
meeting you ass mother fucker are not going to judge anybody else.
The room I don't have to read the room I'm going to put how about this a table for three
a table for three for me Tommy and blogger table for three.
I'll put a fucking red fucking like doily on that shit a table for three
Meet you and vlogger who is like the worst addict shut the fuck up Tommy
I can't wait till we I can't wait till me and Tommy collab with a bottle
We're gonna do it together. It's gonna be like together. It's gonna be me like in the same song as you when you go
Yeah, yeah, Tommy fucking A. Down, down low like the fucking Tommy Junkie James.
Oh wait, did I stutter? Was that the fucking get A?
Wait, is that my fucking reception or is that Stikey?
I don't fucking know, but you know what, time...
Time is gonna tell it's gonna tell Tommy is a motherfucking dyke on a transition
He's on a fucking mission to try to fucking get something on a low on a down low
But guess what Tommy? I'll get you fitty fitty
I need to shut your fucking mouth. Oh, hey, that's all I had to do
Hey, what's trying to be relevant? I said 50 by Alexander wait wait hold on wait a minute
I thought a rock is all about fun. I thought we're disrupting wait. I thought it was all fun
I thought it was fun. Oh, you're mad because we did a little battle
Oh, I cried for a donation. Here's my donation. I need money, by the way. Oh you guys, I'm so hungry. I'm hungry. I'm hungry.
I appreciate your donations.
I am hungry for money though. I need money. I was crying for money. I was crying because all you motherfucking people be donating for fucking drugs and money.
But I need money though. I need money. I'm so fucking hungry.
I need to go get beer. I need to go get alcohol.
No, I can always trash up my fucking beer or fucking wallet. Shut the fuck up.
Or I can get to my fucking penny back. Shut the fuck up. I need money.
What the fuck I need money for. Okay? All right. You're quiet now.
And that's what I have in my fucking wallet. You want my savings? I'll get on there.
I'll give you a hundred dollars right now for a good this song. You do a good this song on me
Good boy. You do a good this song on me. You get a hundo. You gotta make it like very beautiful. I
Well, I
Okay, we'll do this. I'll send it to you. I'll send it to you after you make it. It's gotta be good though
Hondo Hondo you gotta kiss my ass. You gotta say BKG you gotta say I bow down. You gotta say, you know what?
I don't even ask you to shave your head for 150. It's just art. It's art. It's art. It's art.
I want you to like I want you to do your art. I'm motivating you bitch
You think I need money to cry about money?
You want to see more money? You want to see stash of money?
Okay, let's go to the money. Alright, let's go to the fucking money.
Alright, Tommy, I got money for you off your fucking ass.
You like to talk about people, huh?
You like to fucking just complete me.
And then I guess what happens like...
Let me tell you what happens
Money is not the issue. It's about the fucking what you're gonna do. What you're gonna do is like me and you are we gonna do a collab
We're gonna do a collab me and fucking Tommy. It's gonna be Tommy singing
I love you. I love you and then I'm gonna say hey and we're gonna do a rap song
Blah blah blah blah after the panel file is on the panel blah blah blah blah
Yeah, he talked about honey. He said he want he said that my uncle likes to ask me
That's what he said. My uncle. I haven't met my uncle since I was 12 think about that
That's a fuck up. You know uncles are a lot older than their fucking nieces you fucking disgusting piece of shit
you're the fucking scumbag you are disgusting you're a scumbag
you know what below of the fucking lowest i've never met anybody lower than you
i will never fucking forgive you you're disgusting i spent on every existence that you ever had
When he wanted to suck
He wanted to lick his ass for $20 remember when he got fucking blood for it
He is not allowed on any platform. And you know what?
Pito fucking Zea made the statement, but we got fucking Arthur now trying to weasel his fucking weird ass and his oh
You're a Zea lover. You're a Zea lover. I spit on you
What's up, Mojo
what the fuck up go back and suck some gay a dick
arthur i said i'll always own you bitch
i'll always own you bitch
you're a fucking zayas dick sucker
you're a zayas dick sucker
you're a zayadux
uh you're a pdm zayadick
Yeah, I'm hilarious.
Dick got in jail!
He's watching Jeopardy!
Yeah!
We got back in Arthur on the panel by the way
She has an issue with
Peace out fucking Arthur. Have a good call. It was a good show. Thank you for calling in hope I
Told you every fucking time you thought you're fucking messing around
bitch
Let me introduce you to the
Mask God, the Mask God of Big Sucking Crowd
We got Arthur, we got Arthur, we got Arthur K
Before we, listen bitch
You're on the wrong panel for this shit
Before you came along, meet Tommy
I'm fucking blogger. Me, me, me, blogger, I'm fucking Tommy Newpeps, but you knew Zeya, you knew Zeya, Zeya is the fucking progression of fucking events, not fucking peps. Shut the fuck up. Shut the fuck up. Oh, before you came along, we knew fucking peps. We fucking knew peps. But you know what Zeya is? Progression of fucking events. That's where you came from, you fucking media.
Uh-huh.
He's out, PDA.
Alright, PDA.
Alright.
I said I'll call you out.
You want to call me out?
Kev will always be fucking Kev.
Nobody's going to say anything.
She's 32 years old.
You know how old it's fucking Zaya?
45.
Forget another van.
You fucking big fucking hoe.
Yeah.
Let's ask the contestant.
Uh, Tommy.
If you want to call me out.
Call me out.
Whereas like if you're an island would you pick?
by the whole behavior, by the way, shout out to Tommy.
I will be on your island.
Tommy, I'll be on your island.
I'm not meeting on that fucking island.
Uh-uh, I'm not on that fucking island.
Big fat fucking hose.
What did you snip today?
How many drugs or what did you drink today?
All right, you know what?
Less drugs than they have to take for you
to suck fucking Zayah's ankle and butt.
How about that?
So that's just, I need one drug, so you only did one?
No, it means that you did a silver. That's pretty fucking sad. I did it on drugs and you did a silver
But I didn't do this there. I did it to blogger
But guess what you did to a grown-ass fucking man who is a
pronounced fucking weirdo. All right. Okay, so I
Didn't
You did a silver
You hope say he's gay. What's wrong with wanting to suck big
So are you saying you're gay?
I'm telling you
Russian we're having here. Oh wait
Making a confession here
There's nothing wrong with being gay gay is amazing
With gay is good. He is good as long as that you're not saying that you're straight
As long as that you're not working claiming you have a fucking a like the on say
Gay is wonderful, but being a closet gay and being a pedophile like you is
I'm crashing in I'm crashing in I'm crashing in I've been calling anybody else that nobody
fucking said I asked my fucking uncle you did you did Arthur I told you anywhere you
come on the platform anywhere you join anywhere am I
I will fucking always say what are you are you're a zaya dick sucker who is a progression of events
and then you went along and you said that I fuck my uncle and you know what my uncle likes animals
you said I fuck cats you're a sick fucking weirdo none of these people on the panel have ever talked
to me like you have you are weirdo
Shut up to the fucking ETC weirdo, expose the, expose the what, expose the what, shut up, shut up, go back to your fucking sexer hoe, go back to your sexer, go back to your sexer, go back to your fucking disgusting sexer.
Nobody fucking likes that nobody likes there nobody even blogger has to take
about it, although we got a weirdo on the panel called fucking
okay but just because he said something about your uncle don't
mean you got to call him a pretie pal. Yes. Yes. Yes. I will.
He will always be. He will always be. You know what?
Unlike you, unlike any of you, unlike any of you, I love my family, unlike you fucking weirdos.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Fine, thank you.
There he goes with the racist shit.
There he goes, you like that, Aldo?
What if somebody makes fun of your ass who speaks Spanish and says that they like to fuck you?
Shut the fuck up, Eldo.
Don't come up here fucking defending a fucking weirdo, Eldo.
You're crashing me.
Alveda, you drunk too much. You drinking all night, Alveda.
You need to calm the fuck down.
You know what I can do right now is I can make you calm the fuck down.
I will tell you one thing. I will tell you one thing. I you don't have to meet you
I can go live I can do it on my own if anybody comes on my fucking panel and starts talking about your aunt
Let's make a comparison your aunt is older than you right and search like insane because you respect not talking not to you
You come back. I'm talking to elder you respect your aunt. Do you have any aunts?
Although fuck that bitch. All right. I love my fucking uncle. They're nothing. They've done nothing but be like a father to me generous like really really
It's not no, no, no, no, no, it's not a joke when it comes to me. No, there he goes. He called me uncle fucker
All right, thank you. Can you take him or I'll leave he's calling me a fucking
Big Arthur I'll leave I'm not joking with you
Wow, wow, this, that is beautiful.
Bye, see you later.
See ya.
Call me uncle fucker again, bitch. Come on. That's not a reason to kick them though. All right. Listen, Aldo
I don't want to even fucking communicate with you if you think it's okay for somebody to talk about my uncle like that
Because I was giving you a comparison. I was
Where they called them a spirit because you know what it is my uncle is fucking 80 something years old last time
I met my uncle was on the house and my fucking teens in Iran
Okay, I respect my fucking uncle. They're good fucking human beings a good fucking provider to society
They would never talk like that. So when a fucking grown-ass man near 40 and 40 something comes in here and says uncle fucker
I spit on his fucking everything and you too, eldo
Okay
All right, because I never talked about your fucking
And your grandmother shut the fuck up
Yeah, it's funny to you. It's funny. That's where I cut you off, Eldo. That's where I cut you off. I don't give a f**k up your own stupid opinion. You're another f**king piece of s**t to me now.
Go ahead
How would you like it if somebody
Bitch
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Listen vloggers call me many things before me and him I'd like he call me a slurring ugly fucking snake
You can call me everything in the book. You don't have to call my fucking uncle
That's pedophile shit my uncles are like double my fucking age you fucking weirdos
That's sentimental to me. That's my fucking uncle
Bitch, do you know who your answer uncle Dora? Do you know where your sisters and brothers are you stupid?
out of here. Get the fuck out of here. I don't care how drunk I am. You're still gonna fucking
be stupid. I will never fucking talk about people fucking family like that. Shut the fuck up, Eldo.
Beto.
I'm your drunk asshole.
I'm your fucking moron.
As long as guys are to be a fucking man, stand up for something once and for all,
or you're another fucking piece of shit doctor talking about family. Shut up.
I can be a doctor, but you cool with a doctor though
Right
Okay, so like chat says be just crashing out. I would rather get I would rather get dogs
Then have anybody put disrespect on my family members
Yes, yes
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no